[Music]
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Good evening, good day everybody. And uh
I hope everybody is doing well. I hope
wherever you are you're doing great and
we have a lot to discuss today, don't
we? Uh so I'm going to take questions
from the live chat today. So much has
changed and so much is changing and it's
happening so fast that there's no point
me taking questions from the comments.
I'm going to take it all live today like
yesterday. Now before I do that, let me
see who all is there very briefly. I can
see Rahul, Axhat, Draj, Wamshi, Vinup,
um Rigindorj, Shivakumar,
um who else do we have? Prat
Vindar
Menis Rajir Parush Paroo Gupta Anand
Chandak Manugawa Nishant Joun Ma Vines
Venu Gopal VR Mah Babu
Mahtra Abishek Kapoor nearby Takar
Siddik
Shhati online Shik
Vikram Chandra Abin Aurora Arin Patel
Sid Tjas Arindam Das health lifestyle
knowledge Ashwarya Gautami Ashwaryia is
disappointed reef dragon slayer I
understand why Priyanku arav chasia
navin kumar jay dikshit nakul
dakshwara rashmi dungar singh jawan
shiva rajutar kalpuri and so many other
people I will not be able to greet you
all vidi is there lost child and
everybody else all right all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right all right let's get into
the questions I know what questions
could be there and maybe there'll be
something that
something that will surprise us but
let's see okay so what's happened before
I take the questions what has
happened war was going on Pakistan was
on its knees Pakistan was devastated we
had completely suppressed the air
defenses of Pakistan suppression of
enemy air defenses se A we had achieved
it we were hitting we were striking them
at will wherever we
We had gouged out gigantic craters on
their air force and um the runways. We
were hitting them where wherever we
wanted them, right? And they were
begging for mercy, the Pakistanis. And
then what happens? There's a tweet by
Donald J. Trump saying that now there's
a full and whatever ceasefire. And then
Dr. J. Shanker tweets that we have
agreed to a what cessation of of
activity or something. What? Okay.
whatever it is it it is that he said. So
that sort of thing. So he did not use
the term ceasefire Dr. J. Shankar which
is an interesting nuance when it comes
to uh when it comes
to diplomacy. So he says that India and
okay let me put that on the screen so
that everybody can
see this is Dr. SJ Shankr. Uh you can
see my actual Twitter account here. So
Dr. ization. India and Pakistan have
today worked out an understanding on
stoppage of firing and military action.
India has consistently maintained a firm
and uncompromising stand all that stuff
that that we know. We will continue to
do that. So we have today worked out an
understanding on stoppage of firing and
military action right and you can see
people are not happy about
this and what have I said. So this is
the tweet by Donald Trump. After a long
night of talks mediated by the United
States, I am pleased to announce that
India and Pakistan have agreed to a full
and immediate ceasefire. Congratulations
to both countries on using common sense
and great intelligence. Thank you for
your attention to this matter. very
dismissive, very brusk and and and and
and it kind of hyphenates once again
India and Pakistan and he's trying to
portray himself present himself as the
great hero of the matter and we India
and Pakistan are like errant school boys
who are fighting and Trump the
headmaster has come in and he has
stopped the fight right so what did I
tweet in response I I said what are the
ceasefire terms for a viable peace
Pakistan must first of all verifiably
destroy its terror infrastructure and
eliminate all terrorists within or
outside the ISI military complex within
a set time frame which we should decide.
Second, they should hand over all wanted
terrorists to India immediately. Third,
US and its vasals must demonstraably
stop funding Pakistani terrorists
immediately, terrorism immediately.
Fourth, hand over Pakistan occupied
Kashmir. Fifth, free Baljasthan Sindu,
hand over Kaibar Paktunwa to
Afghanistan. that we can we can use that
these terms as a starting point for a
ceasefire uh clearly that's not going to
be the terms
right and uh apparently firing is going
on in Akno and other places now if
firing is going on where's the ceasefire
is my question right and that's that's
where we are right now so that is the
situation now we're going to discuss
that we're going to discuss uh what
happens going forward so let me take
questions and I'm sure everything will
be covered during that. So
now Suraj Kumar Suraj says uh why does
this orange opportunist full of
hypocrisy want to portray himself as the
ultimate negotiator and mediator of
peace? Because he is Trump. He is Donald
J. Trump and we know how he is. is the
this big egoistic guy with a huge ego
and he is the head of the most powerful
nation in the known universe
unfortunately
right so we have been shown the mirror
right now we as in India you're powerful
yeah good job you brought Pakistan to
its knees you shocked the world with the
incredible performance of your air
defenses Incredible. I was
shocked. Okay, I am not easy to impress
me. I was shocked at the e efficacy of
our air defenses. Hats off to our
engineers, scientists and RB people who
are the operators. So, we shocked the
world with the efficacy of our air
defenses. How we were able to bring
everything down and so
on. And yet, we've been able to do all
this. But Mr. Trump comes in. So we the
the power disparity between India and
Pakistan is glaringly
obvious. We could hit them at will. They
could not hit us no matter what they
tried. Yeah, they hit a few civilian
areas and all but uh and that's what
happens in war. People please understand
this. There is no war in which you don't
take any absorb any hits. You have to be
prepared as a nation if you want to be
great and if you want to win wars, you
have to be prepared to absorb some pain
and losses. But you have to the
objective is to of of war is to achieve
your political objectives your
geopolitical
objectives. And the question obviously
is we're going to discuss is have we
achieved our objectives? We're going to
discuss this today. So why did Trump
come in? Because he is this great great
man apparently according to himself full
of himself huge ego. He thinks he's the
greatest negotiator, best negotiator in
the
world and he has the might of the US uh
empire behind him. So the power
differential between India and Pakistan
is glaring, obvious, huge. We could have
finished them if you wanted the next 48
hours. But Trump comes in the way. And
what does it tell you my Indian
friends, all my friends? It tells you
there is a gigantic power differential
between the US and
US. So let's not get
emotional. First of all, I don't think
the story is over. Okay, please
understand the story is not over. But I
would recommend to all of you is I would
recommend that please analyze what's
happening dispassionately without
resorting to emotional to emotions.
Emotions are there. Set them aside and
think about what's happened. We have to
accept the reality first of all that we
are nothing compared to the US in terms
of power. If the US arm twists us, we're
going to have to do what they say. What
leverage does the US have over us? What
leverage does US have over us? Right
now, we are uh negotiating a trade and
and tariffs and all that agreement with
the Americans. The negotiations are in
progress right now. They're in process
right now. Okay. Trump had imposed big
big tariffs on us including and not just
on us and on the whole world. And then
he gave us 90 days to negotiate. And we
said we want to negotiate. Let's let's
find a you know a mutually beneficial
way uh mutually beneficial solution or
agreement to this trade and tariff
matter. So we are negotiating that. So
look one leverage they have over us is
this. If you don't agree to a ceasefire
immediately I'm going to impose 145%
tariffs on you immediately. What could
we do about that? That will destroy our
economy. Right? We want to be the next
China. We want all the Chinese
manufacturing to move to India. So we
have to give Mr. Trump his win. Okay
sir, you want this? Here you have it. We
will we will agree to your ceasefire.
The question is how long will the
ceasefire last? Do you think the
Pakistanis are
capable of
uh honoring a ceasefire? You think they
won't be firing across the border? Mhm.
And we have made one extremely important
doctrinal modification, doctrinal change
today and the Americans have accepted
this and the change is this that going
forward from today onwards from today
onwards any act of terror will be
treated as an act of war by us. So if
there is any terror strike anywhere in
India, we going to treat it as a
declaration of war by Pakistan and then
we're back to square one. And if there's
any ceasefire violation by Pakistan, the
so-called ceile that's that's in force
now. If there's a single bullet that
comes across the border, it's back to
square one. So please understand folks,
I understand the the sense of
disappointment, but let's let's wait and
watch. Let's wait and watch. So Trump of
course look it's not easy to be
hypocrite. You have to be powerful to be
hypocrite. You have to
earn being a hypocrite. So only powerful
nations uh have the right and privilege
of being hypocrites. So don't be upset
about this hypocrisy. Obviously it's
hypocrisy. Don't be upset. Learn. We
want to in the future be in a position
where we can display similar hypocrisy
to them. Double standards. What applies
to me doesn't apply to you. I will hold
you to different standards than me. I'll
do this but you can't do that. That's
where that's when you can do that.
That's where you're really powerful.
That that shows that you've arrived. So
um that's the deal. So that's the thing
about Trump. Now let's see some more
questions. Abage says is this Chanakini
or Prataj syndrome? Why did why did he
not stop the Russia Ukraine war? Look,
yeah. Yeah. Good question. Good
questions. Trump had promised, didn't
didn't he didn't he promised this? That
the moment I come to power as the US
president, within 24 hours, I'm going to
end the Russia Ukraine
war. He had promised that. Has he
succeeded? Trump has failed miserably at
this because Russia is a whole different
beast and he can't arm twist Putin. He
has no leverage over Putin. Now please
understand folks, we are not Russia.
They have a lot of leverage over us. So
is this Chanakiriti or Pritaj syndrome
that we have this enemy on his
knees but we let him go. We haven't let
him go
yet. Understand? So this is being
pragmatic. This is like you know okay
let's not let's let's give them let's
give Trump a win for now for the next 24
to 48 hours maybe 72 hours. maybe one
week the damage we have caused to
Pakistan's military infrastructure
terror infrastructure the Pakistanis
can they can repair that right they can
rebuild the terror factories they will
hide the terrorists whoever is whoever
are alive still obviously most of them
are alive um they will repair their
runways they will repair their airports
they will get new air defense systems
from from the US perhaps from China
perhaps probably not the US otherwise it
will not work for the in India but maybe
they'll get something from China maybe
something from Turkey the Turk the Turks
have been flying planes full of drones
to Pakistan the last 2 three days huh
they have been replenishing Pakistan's
drone supplies the Turks when there were
earthquakes in Turkey we we sent free
medical assistance and we sent personnel
to help people to help pull people out
of rubble
right and what did have the Turks given
us in
return a betrayal remember these people
don't forget Forget Indians love
forgetting things. Indians have a very
short memory. Indians don't have any
sense of history. Unfortunately, today
you know what the west says Indians
don't have a sense of history. It's true
today. It wasn't true in the past. It's
true today because of the education
system. So we don't go into that. Don't
forget the matter of Turkey. Now is this
Pritiad syndrome? Pritiad syndrome would
would be in would be the case if there
was no uh US factor in this ceasefire.
If we had unilaterally given up at this
point without any pressure from the US
then it would be prit prir syndrome
because prituj let the terrorists go
once or twice on his own without anybody
pressurizing him that is pritu syndrome
this is not prati syndrome this is a
much more powerful nation the world's
most powerful nation pressurizing us not
Pakistan they're pressurizing us so this
is being practical and pragmatic and
taking a step back for now I would say
it is more chanaki niti than pira
syndrome but it
will it will be right to call it
chanakiti in retrospect given what
happens over the next two weeks if the
ceasefire actually holds the next two
weeks then Pakistan will be able to
bounce back then it is well then it is
not chanakini chanakini means sometimes
you make compromises take a step back
give the big guy a win and then you go
back that sort of thing so Trump could
not stop the Russia Ukraine war because
He has no leverage over Putin but over
us he can arm twist us. So we have
stepped back for now. For
now. All right. Uh let's see some other
questions. Uh what do we
have? Um Aritra says park we want to
stop India. Donald Heisen say my name.
Yeah I know I know I know I know right.
So now Alicia Alisha says IMF has given
money to Pakistan. Why if they have
already washed their off their hands
from Pakistan? Well, this is a good
question here. Good question here. So,
the IMF has announced some kind of aid
package to Pakistan some
some yeah some bailout for them. I don't
know how many billion dollars maybe one
or two or three billion dollars. Not a
lot of money but yeah it will keep
Pakistan afloat. Now who runs the IMF?
It's the West that runs the IMF. What's
the bigger biggest power behind the IMF?
It's the United
States, right? It's the United States.
So if the United States wants wants
India on its side when it comes to the
China matter, they are trying to isolate
China. Then why are they doing this?
Because they want to have some leverage
over India. As long as Pakistan keeps on
existing and being an absolute nuisance
to deal with for India, as long as that
situation exists,
Pakist Pakistan breaks up tomorrow, then
the US then those countries that emerge
out of the disintegration of Pakistan
which is Balojasthan, Sindluesh, Khibar,
Paktunwa and so on P which comes back
then India will have leverage over that
region.
They won't have any leverage over us or
the region and they won't have any
leverage over us and even the Chinese
leverage over P etc will disappear that
will be a huge win for India that will
make India much more confident and
stronger the US doesn't want that the US
wants India where it is right now
understand this okay so they are okay
with us humiliating Pakistan but not too
far not too much they don't want us to
completely defeat you know the final
defeat to Pakistan
So that's why they have come in the way
the Americans and you have to understand
the American track record. Please do not
forget America's track record.
Indians and the rest of the world should
also know this. I'm sure there are
people from outside outside of India who
are watching. What's the American track
record? Let me give you a brief history
lesson. Let's go back to 1947. In 1947,
Pakistan was cut out of Indian
territory. carved out of Indian
territory by the British with the
involvement of our so-called freedom
fighters some of some our so-called
leaders who were all British stooges
okay the partition of India was not done
democratically there was no referendum
the people of India were not asked to
choose whether we want to give away our
territory or not it was done completely
undemocratically and illegitimately so
it was done the partition of India and
the creation of Pakistan was done to
serve British geopolitical interests in
the Indian subcontinent region and the
in the larger geographical region
especially the Persian Gulf and so on.
So the British did that to serve their
interests not to help us. Then in 1956
the UK became a second rate or third
rate world power after the the their
humiliation in the Suez crisis. Then the
Americans took over the Baton passed
this the the center of power moved from
London UK to Washington DC. It actually
more or less started the process started
in 1944 455 but by 56 it was a feta
complete it was done. So the US becomes
the becomes you know it it takes over
the reigns of the superpower in the
entire structure and then in 1979 the
USSR invades Afghanistan and then
Pakistan offers its services to the US
that we'll be your vasal give us your
dollars we give us your dollars and
teach us how to fight. So the Americans
teach Pakistan new
things. What do they teach Pakistan?
What did the US teach Pakistan? They
taught Pakistan what they had been
implementing in South America
etc. What the CIA had been implementing
there? Reign of terror over the
people. Terrorism
tactics, how to use non-state actors
with plausible deni deniability to
further your state agenda. So they used
the mujahedin to fight the USSR and the
USSR was already crumbling in a in some
way and by the end of the 1980s the USSR
withdrew. So while this was happening in
1979 onwards Pakistan was a wash in US
dollars. The Americans gave them
whatever they wanted arms, ammunition,
greenbacks, US dollars and complete
blanch to do whatever you want. will not
will not bother. You want to do human
rights violations, you want to do
anything, we don't care. Just as long as
you do what we say in Afghanistan,
elsewhere, it works. So then the
Pakistanis obviously the Pakistani
establishment sees India as the great
enemy. They want to destroy India.
That's that's the great dream, right? So
they started funneling all that terror
infrastructure and machinery and the
sharp edge of that into first Punjab,
then Kashmir. By 1989, hundreds of
thousands of Kashmir Hindus were were
evicted. Many of them were killed.
Right? All of this was done with US
financing and funding. And the US knew
exactly what the Pakistanis were doing
and they were okay with that. In the
1990s when I was a kid, India used to
complain to the US. You know, we used to
go with representations to the US and
say that see Pakistan is doing terrorism
against us. And the Americans would say
what are you talking about? This is a
law and order issue and you are not able
to handle law and order issues in your
country. Shame on you. And they knew
exactly what the Pakistanis were doing
because they had taught the Pakistanis
how to create terror networks and
unleash that on on other countries. And
they were funding and financing all of
this and they were giving all the arms
and ammunition. They were okay with
terrorism against India. This continued
until at least 2008 with the Mumbai
attacks. Things may have changed to a
certain extent. And who was the
mastermind of the Mumbai
attacks? Who was it? It was an American
citizen. Not a Pakistani. It was a US
citizen. David Coleman Headley, he's in
prison in the US,
right? India and the US have an
extradition
treaty and he this guy, this terrorist,
this American citizen is wanted, this
American terrorist is wanted by India
but they refuse to hand him over despite
having an extradition treaty because
they have something to hide. So the
Americans are not our friends. Okay,
this is
um whatever arrangement or relationship
we have with them, it is it is not a
long-lasting
thing. It is something that is u that
has come out of uh mutual
convenience. It's because we have a
mutual enemy. They have no love for
India. They have bled India in the past
and they have more love for Pakistan
than than for India because Pakistan is
culturally more like them a monotheistic
culture people of the book we are
polytheists we are heathens we are
pagans in in their terminology so please
understand Pakistan is still valuable to
the US India is more valuable but they
don't want Pakistan to completely
completely disintegrate that is the deal
we understand this if there is any
friend that we have geopolitically in
the world Today the closest we have to a
friend today is
Russia. Okay. But it we want to be we
want to have good relations with
everybody. We want to work with
everyone. We are we as a nation for
whatever reason because of of the two
and a half centuries of British
occupation we are very comfortable with
western culture with Anglo-Saxon
culture. So we know how to deal with
them. We know better how to deal with
them today than 20 years ago. So we are
dealing with everybody and this is the
process. But when it comes to this
ceasefire matter, I say let's wait and
watch. Let's wait and
watch.
Um, Shah says historic blunder. We
disagree with Modi government decision.
Please, please be a little patient. If
the ceasefire holds and Pakistan gets to
bounce back, then it's a disaster. It's
not a victory for India. And already I
I'll tell you if you go to Twitter, if
you go to the western media, they will
already be hard at work trying to paint
this as a Pakistani victory that India
was made India was forced to back off by
Pakistan and India was not strong enough
to defeat Pakistan and finish
Pakistan and Pakistan has been able to
withstand the Indian assault and
Pakistan is resilient and next time we
will defeat India. That's the narrative
that will be spun
immediately. That process has already
started. So if the ceasefire holds and
in the next one or two weeks to one or
two months to 3 months or 6 months if
Pakistan is able to bounce back, rebuild
its infrastructure and all that then
essentially what we have done in the
past 72 hours this incredible military
uh performance it's going to count for
nothing.
So let's wait and watch what happens
next next few days next I think 24 to 48
to 78 hours I think 72 hours I think
things will change things are very
likely to
change says has India lost the golden
opportunity not yet not yet I think we
still have one week in which to in which
to make further progress on the
matter we still it's it's not gone the
opportunity is not gone we have 7 to 10
days. If if nothing happens militarily
in the next 7 to 10 days, then we are
losing the
opportunity. Right now we have a golden
opportunity. An opportunity that comes
once in 80
years. The opportunity to end this
threat once and for all. What's you know
what's the objective of war? The
objective of war is to do what you can't
do diplomatically.
It's to achieve
your the the achieve what is
required in the in in in the pursuit of
your national interests through
non-diplomatic means. So it's it's about
national interest. It's about achieving
your objectives and goals and it's about
removing threats. We have been saddled
with this permanent cancer, this
permanent threat Pakistan on our western
border. And as long as it
exists, it's going to be a threat for
us. If we let it go now, in 6 months
they'll be
back. Then they'll be claiming victory
from today onwards that we won. We we
stopped India from defeating us. We have
been resilient. And then in 6 months, 1
year, whenever, whatever, they make
emerge even stronger with Chinese help
or whatever. This is the opportunity
that we have today. Today we have got
them exactly where we want them. They
are on their knees. Their air defenses
have been wiped out. Their airports are
inoperational. Their F-16s can't take
off or
land. They are humiliated. The people of
Pakistan have seen the importance of the
Pakistan military. Sinduh can rise.
Balojasthan is already trying to rise.
Taliban will be waiting and watching.
Give us an opportunity. We'll take back
Kyber
Pakula. So we have this opportunity once
in 80 years. I have said this many
times. I think Prime Minister Modi is
probably the greatest prime minister
we've ever ever had. And Mr. Modi
obviously to be to be a great leader,
you must be an ambitious leader. And you
must have ambitions for the greatness of
your country. not personal ambitions but
ambitions for the greatness and progress
of your country. And Mr. Modi has the
opportunity that no prime minister has
had since 1971 of finishing Pakistan
once and for all. If he achieves that,
he will be remembered by Indians for
centuries as a
Mahapurush. This is his opportunity. And
do you think he doesn't know that? I
think he knows that. Do you think he'll
give it up that easily? Let's wait and
watch. I don't think so. Not yet gone.
The opportunity is not yet gone. Now
let's take some other questions. Uh
geopolitical dub says will it affect
Prime Minister Modi's image? Right now
there's a big sense of disappointment in
the country. We had Pakistan on their
knees. They are still on their knees.
It'll take them one or two weeks to even
start standing up again.
Right? If we let them go away, then it
will affect Prime Minister Modi's image.
It will.
But we have time. So let's see what Mr.
Modi is able to accomplish. Right now
Trump has come in the way. This is not a
friendly action by Trump. Okay. He is he
is trying to deny us the military
victory that we essentially have already
won that we have already earned. We have
not won it yet. We have not achieved it
yet. But we are on the verge of
achieving
it. We have shown the entire world the
hollowess of Pakistan's nuclear
blackmail. Hm. They used to keep
threatening us in the world entire world
that if India crosses even 1 cm into
Pakistani held territory then we will
unleash the Islamic bomb the nuclear
bomb. What happened to that? We have
destroyed their blackmail that nuclear
blackmail. We have hit them at the heart
of the military Pakistani military ISI
terrorism complex. We've hit them
everywhere we wanted. We have hit them
at will. We've destroyed their
infrastructure. First terrorist
infrastructure then military
infrastructure. The air defense is wiped
out.
We have done all this, right? Their
ammunition is running out. They're
running out of
ammunition. But you know the west is
saying this was just a
skirmish. Apparently there were air
battles about like in the A.M. today
early morning. Apparently we have
brought down Pakistani fighter
planes. The government hasn't said that
so I'll not go further into it.
But we have achieved a lot and we are on
the verge of achieving something
bigger. See this will be if if the
ceasefire holds this whatever happened
the past 72 hours will be termed by the
west as a skirmish or a small conflict.
This what happened in the past 48 hours
is way bigger than the cargill war. The
cargill war was localized. This was all
over the place. We've hit Pakistan
everywhere.
But the west will portray this as
nothing but a skirmish. And they'll say,
"What happened? There's no territorial
change. Nothing has changed. So if you
want to to
to seal the victory, the lines on the
map must
change. See today what's the situation?
Pakistan's air defenses are destroyed.
They are
helpless. We can send a drone, a
helicopter, slowmoving thing into
Pakistan. It'll be hard for them to
bring it
down. So, their air defenses are gone.
Their fighter planes can't take off or
land on all those destroyed airports and
the cratered
runways. What's the next thing we should
have done? A pulse pause war. Take back
P. That could have happened tonight or
tomorrow. If that doesn't happen, if no
territory change happens, then you can't
say you've won the war. You can't even
say it was a war. They'll just say it
was a series of strikes against each
other. So if the ceasefire holds and
Pakistan goes back to what it was doing,
then it will affect Prime Minister
Modi's image. No question about
it. Um Niraj Kant says Pakistan being
Pakistan, we all know that this day will
come back again terrorism in four to
five years. How can India grow ourselves
militarily and economically so pressure
from the US can be ignored? Yeah, great
question. Uh today the US can arm twist
us right they have done it today but we
are not the same beast we were in 2019.
In 2019 the Pakistanis they were they
were much more confident and we were not
able to do what we have done in the last
72 hours in 2019 the Bala court uh thing
and all that right and before that we
did surgical strikes very very quietly
we had did not have the confidence to
launch air strikes like Balakot. So
every few years we're getting more and
more powerful, more more and more
confident, right? So what needs to
happen is we have to grow
economically. With economic growth comes
material growth, material prosperity,
better living standards, more confidence
in the people and with milit with with
that comes military growth and your
military strength becomes more powerful.
Right? So right now we are a 4.5 roughly
trillion dollar economy. Maybe in 5
years hopefully we are a 10 trillion
dollar economy. That needs to happen as
soon as possible. It's just an arbitrary
number 10 trillion. I don't care if it's
9 trillion. I don't care if it's 12
trillion. Should be in the vicinity of
10 trillion. Then we'll be twice as
powerful as what we are today. Right?
And then even China will treat us in a
different will will regard us
differently. The Chinese have been
saying since 2018 or so that India has a
much higher capacity to take risks and
see what we did in the past 72 hours.
That's called risk risk takingaking.
So Pakistan being Pakistan if we allow
them to escape from the situation they
are in right now then they are going to
come back
stronger. The problem has to be solved
once and for all. If you have cancer you
don't keep it in your body. You have to
excise it and remove it and destroy
it. So um we have to solve this problem.
It has it has to happen soon and we will
never have as great an opportunity as we
have right now today at whatever time it
is. See to go to war you need a just
cause for war. You have to show to the
world that we are the victim and we have
a just cause and right now we have all
of
that. Um so let's see let's see what
happens in next 24 to 48 hours. Let's
see.
They just says what about the Indust
water treaty and PK? Are we to do
nothing about against Pakistan and wait
for the next terror attack? If Trump
succeeds in imposing this ceasefire,
then yeah, we are essentially in a
situation when we where we are waiting
for the next terror attack. Uh some
changes have happened. The doctrinal
changes happened. We have made it very
clear to everybody that any future
terror attack against us will be treated
as a declaration of war. So which which
means that we can go back to war. But
then if you wait for 6 months for the
next terror attack, it will obviously
happen. and the Pakistanis are a
terrorist nation. You wait for 6 months,
they will have repaired everything. They
would have rebuilt their infrastructure
and then we would start from zero again.
We have already gone 70% of the way to
destroying Pakistan today. So it doesn't
make sense to wait. So we have to find a
way to continue this war in our favor
and and take it to the logical
conclusion. Now let's say the the
ceasefire lasts unfortunately h what
happens to P? Nothing happens to P.
Pakistan continues holding PK and they
can keep saying that the Kashmir matter
is a disputed territory. Kashmir is a
disputed territory and we and Kashmir
matter is an international matter. They
can keep on saying it. We have the
opportunity to end this so-called
dispute
today. Today if Mr. Modi gives the order
by tomorrow morning we will have P. I
promise you we we are in that situation
right
now.
Okay. So if the ceasefire holds then
forget about P. It won't come back. This
is the golden opportunity. This is the
golden opportunity. Indust treaty is
gone. Forget about it. Even if the
ceasefire holds, we're not going to
honor the Indust treaty. Uh so yeah, the
Americans are okay with that, I suppose.
Yeah. All right. What other questions do
we have? We're going to have a lot a lot
of
questions. Um okay. Pratam says, "What
could happen in the next 24 to 48 hours?
Ceasefire violation by Pakistan. That's
what could happen. or a terror attack
somewhere maybe in Jammu and Kashmir
maybe somewhere else now we don't want
terror attacks because it hurts our
civilians our our innocent men women and
children but Pakistan is a terrorist
nation and sooner or later there will be
more terrorist attacks if we let them go
scot-free today if we let them go today
if Mr. Trump succeeds then Pakistan
remains a terrorist nation a terror
entity that is financed by the west by
the IMF and so on and then we have
failed and there was no point doing what
we have done the past 72 hours it's it's
like what happened in the past many
times so what could happen in the next
24 to 40 years 48 hours um ceasefire
violations across the border the LOC or
wherever I I hear it's happening right
now so
um let's see let's
If nothing happens, if the Pakistanis
remain disciplined and then don't fire
any bullets across the border, then the
ceasefire holds because we are supposed
to revisit the the situation on the 12th
of May. Today is the 10th of May. So 48
hours we revisit the situation and then
we can decide what to do. Um I think we
have gone way past the the the situation
where we used to give evidence to the
world that Pakistan is a terrorist
nation. We don't have to give any more
evidence. So that has changed. But in
the next 24 to 48 hours, it's possible.
It's actually quite likely that the
Pakistanis will try will try some
mischief. If they fire a single bullet
across the border, international border
or the line of control, then I think we
should take the opportunity to finish
them off. Enough is
enough. All
right. Somia Sat says, "What is this
12th of May meeting all about? Will
India be deciding ceasefire conditions?
I think it's too early for me to say
what's going to happen on on on the 12th
of May. I mean, I just heard before I
came into the live stream that Mr. Trump
has imposed a ceasefire and we have
accepted that. So, um, Mr. Dr. J.
Shankar tweeted just now that we will
what what did he say? We are going to
No, he did not tweet about that as far
as I know, but maybe something else has
happened. So, I'm not going to monitor
it in in real time right now.
But uh on the so the ceasefire is going
to be reviewed I suppose on the 12th of
May. I don't think India and Pakistan
will send people who will you know
officials who will meet each other or
something. Uh but let's wait and watch.
I'm not sure what has been announced. I
am sure the government must have done
some kind of uh briefing media briefing
or something in which we must have
explained what the terms of the
ceasefire etc. are. We'll have to see
but u so we we'll see. I don't know who
is deciding the ceasefire conditions,
what the ceasefire conditions are. Once
again, let me tell you according to me
what the ceasefire conditions, the terms
of the ceasefire conditions should be.
Let me put that once again on the
screen. This is my perspective. It may
or may not be the government's
perspective. This is my perspective.
What are the ceasefire terms? I'm asking
over here and then I'm saying that for a
viable peace, Pakistan must agree to
these terms. First of all, Pakistan must
verifiably destroy its terror
infrastructure and eliminate all
terrorists within and outside of the ISI
military uh complex and this has to
happen within a set time frame not not
someday in the future. No, you have
let's say 7 days to do it or something
that sort of thing. Second, they have to
hand over all wanted terrorists to India
immediately. In third, US and its was
demonstrably stop funding Pakistani
terrorism fourthwidth immediately
because Pakistani terrorism happens
because the west has been funding it.
The US has been funding it. So that
condition has to apply to the US not to
Pakistan. Fourth, they have to hand over
P if they want a ceasefire. And fifth,
free Bljasthan, Sindu and so on. That
are that to me seems like a reasonable
set of conditions and terms for
accepting a ceasefire with Pakistan. The
US obviously will not accept those
terms. Right? So the US has come in the
way of
India. Yes. Our great friend the US our
great friend Mr. Trump has come in the
way. Blood bonger says what's going to
happen with the allegedly captured
Pakistan pilot.
Look, the past 3 days
um reports have come out um pretty
credible reports that multiple Pakistani
fighter planes have been brought down
within Indian territory. I'll not give
the number because it is not confirmed
and the government of India has not made
any statements to this effect. The
government of India has not said
anything about any Pakistani planes
being brought down anywhere within India
or outside of India. But I have heard
credible reports the past 2 three days.
I've been seeing social media monitoring
what's happening. I have seen credible
reports pretty credible reports okay
from very credible journalists and
people on the ground that multiple
Pakistani planes have been shot down by
India. Okay. And then they they went
quiet after reporting that even DD news
apparently reported something like that.
So that's pretty credible. DD News is
part of the government. But then they
went quiet about this. So let us
consider a scenario a hypothetical
scenario in which we have brought down a
certain number of Pakistani fighter
planes within our territory. On the
other side of on the Pakistani side I
promise you Pakistani planes have gone
down. I promise you. But they will not
they will not admit that on our side
it's quite likely planes have come down
and uh when plane when when a fighter
plane comes down it's shot down and the
process of shooting it down it involves
certain kinds of munitions. It's you
know you have fragmentation proximity
fuses with fragmentation warheads which
uh release shrapnel and riddle the plane
with holes which is why it stops
functioning and goes down. And when you
riddle an aircraft with holes, you can
also riddle the pilots with holes. So
often times the pilots die in the
process. And that's yeah, that's part of
the game. Sometimes the pilots survive.
Maybe it's a 50/50 thing. So let's say
let's say hypothetically, just for the
sake of argument, two planes were come,
two PR planes were brought down. It's
probable that at least one pilot would
have survived, would have ejected and
would have parachuted down into Indian
territory. In that case, that pilot
would have been recovered alive.
So in case such a thing has happened in
this completely hypothetical scenario
then those pilots Pakistani pilots would
be in Indian custody and they would be
enjoying Indian hospitality and we would
be interrogating them and extracting
whatever intelligence information etc we
need to extract from them. Now if you
announce to the world officially that we
have recovered X number of pilots then
people like Trump etc can apply pressure
on you to to repatriate them. They can
say the Pakistanis gave back aan so you
need to give back these pilots. So
that's why in this hypothetical scenario
that we have captured someone multiple
people possibly we stay quiet about
that.
So that's the deal and that person if we
don't acknowledge the existence of the
person that person remains in our
custody indefinitely maybe whatever
whatever period of time all
right okay what next do we
have okay I was trying to okay let's
take this one sky fragrances end game
cannot be achieved without crossing the
nuclear threshold what's your view
that's an interesting question and it
has to be taken seriously it has to be
taken seriously
At the end of the day,
if Pakistan is going to let's say
hypothetically in the future, maybe in
the next one or two weeks be in a
situation where it's going to break up
completely and the Pakistan military
loses all control of the country, they
will be very tempted possibly to use
nukes. Now what happens? Good question.
What happens? How does it happen? So
let's say they want to fire nukes in
India. What delivery mechanisms do they
have to send nukes to whatever
destination in India? H they have
missiles. They either have cruise
missiles or or or or ballistic missiles.
Those those ghastly names Gori Gaznavi
etc. those things. Now in the past 72
hours we have seen the capabilities of
our air defense systems. We brought
everything down. Yes. Last night they
fired a long range missile at
Delhi. It was aimed at Delhi. It was on
its way to Delhi and we brought it down
over SRSA in
Hana. Okay. Now I don't know which
component of our air defense system was
used to bring it down to shoot this
missile down there. It's it's all over
the news. Okay. It's all over social
media. The incredibly loud bang with
this huge flash which is captured by
CCTV cameras.
So, so they have this longrange missile
with possibly a 400 km range which we
brought it which we brought down. We may
have used maybe an S400 system perhaps.
I'm just speculating. I don't have
information. I'm not giving any actual
intelligence to anyone. I'm just
speculating. It could be an S400 system
which everybody knows we have. We also
have a Barak system. Barak 8. Everybody
knows it's been known for the past 15
years. We have it. And then there's the
Akash SAM which is an absolutely
superstar system which has been proven
in the last 72 hours. So even that is a
possibility. So one of these three
things possibly brought down the long
range missile that the Pakistanis had
fired at Delhi. Now what was the
warhead? Was it a conventional warhead?
Was it a nuclear warhead? Because when
you fire when you fire a long-range
missile then the recipient has no way of
knowing what's coming towards him. The
warhead could be a conventional
explosive warhead. It could be a nuclear
explosive warhead. So when somebody
fires a long-range missile at you, that
itself is a red line. And
we we were mature enough to not respond
to that. We've responded by destroying
their airports. Sure. And by setting
their their skyline on on fire last
night. So we have very potent air
defenses. And I assure you, I don't have
actual knowledge. I am just telling you
that it makes sense that we have done
this that every major city of India has
its own highquality air defense system.
I don't know what air defense system it
could be. It could be multiple layers of
air defenses like we have at the border.
It could be S400. It could be Akash
SAMS. It could be Barack. It could be
pad defense pritu air defense system and
so on. So even if Pakistan fires
ballistic missiles with nuclear warheads
on us, it is most likely that they will
fail to hit any target. H So let's say
we use the Priti air defense system to
take out an incoming ballistic missile.
How does a ballistic missile work? It
has a parabolic trajectory, not
hyperbolic, parabolic trajectory. You'll
learn this in high school, parabolic
motion and physics anyway. So it has a
parabolic trajectory. The ballistic
missile will first exit the atmosphere.
The atmosphere limit is is said to be
the the 100 km mark above the surface.
So it'll go above the atmosphere like
this like this and then it re-enters the
atmosphere and it goes towards the
target. So the prefer defense system has
two components. There is one missile
that is an exo atmospheric interceptor
which will take out the incoming missile
that we've already detected by radar. It
will take it out outside of the
atmosphere before it re-enters. Now in
case let's say it fails then we have a
second missile that goes out with the
prefer defense which will intercept the
incoming missile at about 40 or 50 km
above the earth which is
endoatmospheric and these are extremely
accurate
missiles. We also have an ASAT
capability, anti-satellite capability,
which is a a kill vehicle, which is
obviously launched by a rocket, a
missile, which can take out
satellites at an altitude of up to about
1,000 km above the Earth's surface. We
can take out a satellite with pinpoint
accuracy. And the intercept is done with
an object, a satellite that's moving at
at least 10 kilometers per second.
That's faster than a bullet. And we can
take it out with pinpoint precision. And
I promise you this system, this ASAT
system can also be used to take out
incoming ballistic missiles. My point is
if Pakistan even tries to hit us nuclear
with with nuclear weapons, it is most
likely they will fail. Most likely.
But let us consider a different
scenario. Let's say hypothetically and
unfortunately they succeed in detonating
a nuke over an Indian population center.
H what happens then they're finished.
It's not mutually assured
destruction. The if they fire 20 or 50
they may be able to hit us once perhaps.
Okay.
Hypothetically if that happens they have
no air defense left today. If they
detonate a new code any Indian civilian
center it is bye-bye for them and our
missiles are going to hit. They have no
air defenses. So you understand it is
suicide for Pakistan to try something
like this. What if they use a
battlefield tactical nuke? A tactical
nuke is a low yield nuclear weapon.
Hiroshima scale 10 20 kilot tons of
equivalent of TNT let's say let's say we
are making a move on P and these people
see that you know we're going to lose P
what if the detonate a battlefield nuke
nuclear weapon on the battlefield well
that's something we will have to
consider the government of India will
have to have its own calculations
obviously it has and that doctrine and
that escalation ladder is not available
for public consumption It should not be
but we have to trust the government that
we have everything in place. So all
these calculations all this war gaming
is done during peace time. It's like
this. Let's say you want to win you want
to win a gold medal med medal at the
Olympics at the 100 m race the sprint.
You don't put all of your energy and
effort during the final race. All your
energy all the sweat all the tears they
are spent during training.
The easiest part of winning the gold
medal is the last race. The worst part,
the most difficult and painful part is
that four years of training that comes
before that. Similarly, if you want to
prepare for a war, you have to prepare
during peace time. You have to sweat and
bleed during peace time so that you can
win the war easily. So, I promise you
that's been done. All the war gaming has
been done. All the scenarios have been
gamed out and the doctrine is in place.
What if the Pakistanis detonate a
battlefield nuke? What if they detonate
try to detonate and you over a
population center what if they succeed
and so on. So we have all the scenarios
gamed
out. Um so in case the nuclear threshold
is is crossed I think we have it very
well covered. Look in war if you want to
achieve your objectives sometimes often
times most times you have to absorb some
losses and when you're dealing with an
entity like Pakistan
um achieving the ultimate objective may
cost us a little bit it's it's if we
don't have the stomach for it we should
not aim to be like everybody wants to be
a super superpower right to be a
superpower to to even think of being a
superpower to cross the hurdle of
eliminating Pakistan, you have to pay
some price for it. It's only through
through such by paying the right price
that you go towards
greatness. So I am not an advocate of
nuclear war. I I have said this so many
times. That's the last thing any
civilized person should should envisage,
you know, using nuclear weapons. But
they exist and they can be used. So we
have to be prepared for it. That's my
point.
All
right. Matrix says, "Why can't why can't
India despite having 1.5 billion people
reject the US like Israel, Ukraine, and
Iran? At the end, the US also needs
India to counter China." Look, it's a
process. We can't we can't say no to the
US. You can't say no to no to Trump
because he he will impose some immediate
pain on you and he if you say no to him,
he will publicly humiliate you. You
don't we don't want to go down that
ladder. We play a different game. I'm
I'm pretty sure that this is you know
what's happened right now. The Okay,
breaking news. Ceasefire violations at
Aknore and Mandar ceasefire violations
like they say in Hindi. What's the what
do they say? Picture of Bbaki. Wait and
watch. Okay. Right now BSF is countering
the violations. I have a TV on the other
side of the screen like yesterday of the
of the lens.
Uh yeah, ceasefire violations. So what
happened to Mr. Trump's
ceasefire? Are we supposed to tolerate
this? My point is wait and watch. Wait
and watch. He the US does need us. So
once the Pakistanis do cease his fire
violations and then we go back to the
situation. Then Trump can't say that we
we did not pay heed to him. We go to
Trump and say look you wanted a
ceasefire. We agreed. We put it on the
record. Mr. Dr. Jashankar put it on the
record that we have agreed to a
ceasefire or a sessation of law. firing
or military activities. We accepted it
but then the Pakistanis force overhand
now you can't blame us now you would
blame
Pakistan I think that's the direction in
which this is going to go there are
ceasefire violations happening right now
right now multiple locations across the
LOC by park army this is
unacceptable this is
unacceptable they need to finish
Pakistan I think this is the opportunity
Mr. Modi needs. Mr.
Modi, this is the opportunity he needs.
The Pakistanis are handing it on a
plate, on a platter. So, let's let's
wait and watch. This is not over by by a
long distance. This is not over. This is
not
over.
Um, listen, I don't I I understand the
sentiments. I understand the emotions. I
understand the disappointment but I
would urge my dear viewers I would urge
you to not give in to
negativity. The moment something goes
wrong you don't say start crying and
saying that we have lost. Please I
implore you all be more resilient be
more positive. Life is a long game. Life
is a long game. This war is a long game.
We haven't lost.
We have encountered a setback in the
form and shape in the shape and form of
Mr. Donald Trump. We have to find the
right way to negotiate that and overcome
the hurdle. And listen, we will say
this. We agreed to your ceasefire. Now
look at what's happening. It's the the
border is live now. I can see flashes on
the
sky. We haven't lost my friends. Please
please don't be negative like this.
Please don't be negative like this.
Uh, ceasefire is broken. There we have
it. There we have it. Ceasefire
violations. There we have
it. Okay. Shria says, I have zero
questions or doubt on my army and my
nation. As you are right, and you're
right to have no doubt, the army has
proven itself. What they have achieved
in the past 72 72 hours is nothing short
of a complete humiliation of the
Pakistani military. Anyhow, so there's
no doubt about the army and the nation
in the nation. We are a great nation. We
are a great nation and we got to go back
to where we were. Now IMF has approved a
1.8 billion uh you know waiver loan or
or thing to Pakistan arms while pressing
for deescalation. Your comments on the
matter how do we tackle? We have to
remember at all times the west is not
our enemy. uh is not our friend. It's
not our friend. It's not our enemy. They
don't have anything personal against
India except for us being polytheists.
Okay? But they want a certain balance of
power everywhere in the world and they
want the situation to persist. Now if
they see everywhere you look on the map,
there's a certain geopolitical
calculation. You can put a number on
each country which is the the hard power
score of the country and then you can
have a balance in each region. So in
what they call South Asia, which I call
the Indians incontinent, they want a
certain balance of power. In Central
Asia, they want a certain balance of
power and they want various coalitions
and blocks to work in different ways. In
the the 2000s, they completely upended
the balance of power in West Asia by by
eliminating Iraq as an entity, right? So
they are capable of doing that. So my
point is the the West, the US is not our
friend. They don't they will want to
work with us as long as China is a
threat and then they will look at us as
a threat. Remember this remember this if
in the next 10 20 years India starts
rising like China they will look at us
also as a threat and they will treat us
exactly the way they are treating China
today. Remember this remember that we
have no friends geopolitically.
The only nation that we don't have any
issues with actually is Russia and
Russia itself is in a certain situation
right now that they have to align align
not ally but align with China. So my
comments are that the west is playing
this game and it's no surprise they're
playing this game. They have always
played this game. It's nothing new that
they will play India and Pakistan
against each other. They'll play India
against China and they will use they
will want to use India as a pawn on
geopolitical chessboard against China
and just to keep India in line and keep
India behaving as they want they will
use Pakistan as a counter as as a
pressure point. So if India is on the
verge of destroying Pakistan it's a loss
for the west and they understand
Pakistan very well and they want it to
continue to exist. So that's why they
are propping up the terror machine. The
west has a long track record of
supporting funding and financing
terrorism especially Pakistani
terrorism. Okay. They they try to
portray themsel to put themselves on a
pedestal and to to moralize and and to
show that you know we are morally
superior to you but they have been
funding Pakistani terrorism for
decades. Okay. What is next? What is
next? So once again I'm getting this
ceasefire is violating again is being is
being vi is is violated again. Okay
let's take this question. Roshan Rahman
says America doesn't want its asset to
be destroyed so that they can keep the
keep up the pressure on India. Will
Trump give India some concessions in the
upcoming trade deal if India follows the
ceasefire? That must have been the
promise. Look they will not put this out
in the public that in exchange for
accepting the ceasefire we have promised
these these these things to India. No,
this is all done behind closed doors. So
you are absolutely right Roshan that
some such promises would have been made
behind closed doors. Diplomacy has two
facets. One facet is the public facet in
which you are very well well behaved,
very polite and you yeah you yeah
there's a certain etiquette certain way
of behaving in public when it comes to
diplomacy and when it comes to
diplomats. They're very swave people,
very polished people. They speak very
well. they all always under great
control and so on. One of the great
diplomats is Mr. Lavrov, Sergey Lavrov.
I mean a legend. Another is Dr.
Jashankar and so on. So that's the
public face of diplomacy. All smiles or
if not smile, if you're not smiling, if
you're with the enemies, you're very
polite. But there's a private aspect to
diplomacy which happens behind closed
doors. What happens behind closed doors
is often nothing short of
bullying and threatening. Outright naked
threats are issued behind closed
doors. Arm twisting in every possible
way. Physical threats to the
diplomats. Everything is is okay behind
closed
doors. And when you are a way more
powerful nation, you do that to
everybody including your allies if if
required. H so I am sure that it did not
go to that extent in the you know uh
talks between India and the US for
achieving the ceasefire. The US must
have said you guys need to cease fire
now. So the Indians would have said our
people would have said okay you want a
ceasefire we'll give it to you. We'll
give we we will give Donald Trump that
win. What do you give us in return? This
is what we need. This this this this and
these are our conditions that if
Pakistan does terrorism again, we're
going to treat it as a declaration of
war. If they break the ceasefire on
their side, then we're going to go back
to war and so on. So certain conditions
would have been accepted and yes, some
concessions must have been promised to
India in the upcoming trade deal. So all
of that is part of the negotiations and
then what when all of that is finalized,
the the announcement is made. That's how
it works in diplomacy. Very interesting
question and very good question. Now,
um Adita says, "I agree that Pakistan is
going to do ceasefire violations and the
agreement with Trump will become null
and void." And that's happening right
now. Blackout in Patan Court. Blackout
in Patan Court. Here we go
again. So, uh you see Pakistan is a very
reliable nation.
You see this Pakistan is a super blast
heard across Sinagar. Drone sightings in
parts of Jammu and
Kashmir. Here we go my friends. Here we
go my friends. We are back to square
one. Mr. Donald Trump please do not now
pressurize India. You pressurize
Pakistan. Pressurize Pakistan. We agreed
to the ceasefire and I promise you we
have a professional army who will do
what they they're told to do by the
government. That is part of the honor
code of the army. They are disciplined.
So here we have it. Simei also says
ceasefire is
violated. Well now you don't let
Pakistan off the
hook. You don't let Pakistan off the
hook. I had made this tweet. I'll show
you one second. Give me a second. I had
made this tweet. Where was it?
Where was it? Let me give me a second.
Yeah, this is the this is the tweet I
made after that first live stream two or
three days ago. This is the tweet I
made. I made this on the 8th of May,
11:15 p.m. right after I ended that live
stream on that day, the e emergency
episode. I said, "We are at war,
friends." And I said I put my neck out
and I said within the next 2 to 14 days
India will inflict a comprehensive
military defeat on Pakistan and the
borders will change permanently. And I
made this tweet on the 8th of May. So if
you add 14 to that it's May
22. You see, so I I may still be
vindicated by the 22nd of May now that
these
terrorists have violated the
ceasefire. You don't let them go now.
This is the
opportunity for us to go forward and
this is the opportunity for us to tell
Donald Trump, Mr. Trump, Mr. President,
we tried. We did what you said. Now we
are not to blame. You deal with Pakistan
now. We will not go back to a ceasefire
now. Enough is
enough. So here we have it. Now it it
depends how far this goes. Blasts here
heard across Trinagar. Oh my goodness. I
can see flares and lights in the sky.
Here we have it. Here we have it. Okay.
Let's let's see how this how this
develops. Mythical Sati says now I
understand why the government did this.
Look, the government acted logically.
You can't say no to Mr. Trump. You can't
say no to him. You we need Mr. Trump on
our side. He doesn't have any enmity or
hatred towards India. He sees all the
nations as various kinds of assets and
he actually likes India to a certain
extent, maybe to a good extent, but he
wants us to tow the line and he's super
powerful. So, we have to give him that
respect that he actually deserves. What
deserves respect in geopolitics? only
one thing power only one thing and he is
the most powerful person in the world
right now you have to give him the
difference and the respect and we did
that and now the Pakistanis have broken
the ceasefire now we blame them because
they are to blame not
us all right Mlevin is asking
interesting questions kind of off topic
but not quite off topic not quite off
topic so I'll take it good question the
US army has been spotted setting up camp
in
Bangladesh I it's good to know that
people know about this Now you might you
think they might escalate the war into
Manipur. Do you think they're trying to
make a deal cookie line in exchange of
Pakistan? I don't know. I can't
speculate. I will not speculate on air
in public. But I have my suspicions. But
it's a good question you asked. I'm
sorry I can't answer this because it's
an evolving ongoing situation which is
very very
u um you know it's it's crucial to our
national security. So it doesn't it's
not a good practice for me to say
anything about this right now. But you
are asking good questions and I
appreciate that and it's good that you
are aware of what's happening.
Yes, free hand has been given to the
BSF. I think soon enough it'll go beyond
the BSF. So it has to once
again follow a certain pattern of
escalation. We start with the BSF,
right? Capilh Gujarati says, "Is this an
act of war? I see no other way of
looking at it." Yes, it's a good
question and you are right. I I think
it's an act of war. A ceasefire has to
be honored by both sides. Once you agree
to a ceasefire, not a single bullet must
come across the border. Otherwise, it's
end of now. Now, what do we do? Because
you are using small arms fire. So, we
only use small arms fire. No, you
violated the agreement. You violated the
trust and you have to be punished to the
fullest extent. Now, end of story.
Akur. Oh man. Drone sightings in Jammu
and Kashmir.
Here we have it. Omar Abdullah has
tweeted that Shinagar Yeah. Shinag
blasts in
Shinagar. Janil says after the ceasefire
violation now is there a possibility of
a ground incursion now and change the
borders. You see my friends that is the
next logical
step. Pakistan has
proven, it's proving right now in real
time that it is not an honorable country
and it cannot be trusted. They were
begging for a ceasefire and now they
have broken the
ceasefire. They cannot be trusted. So
they so what needs to be done? They have
to be punished. And now that they have
violated the ceasefire, we have to
permanently end their capacity and
capability for violating more
ceasefires. Now that they have not
honored their agreement, we going to
end we have to end their ability to
dishonor agreements in the past in in
the in the
future. How do you do that? By
dismantling Pakistan entirely and by
defanging the Pakistan military
completely. And at the least we do a
pulse pause
war lightning lightning fast non-b blitz
creek warfare frontal warfare wide
essentially essentially what it means is
you take back P. Now you have suppressed
their their air defenses. Now you
suppress their ground capabilities by
by nice means. They have those nice
means. Then you make a march. By morning
it should be in Muzafarabad and wherever
else needs to happen. Facts on the
ground need to change by morning. That's
what I would say. Let's see. This is
going to be another big night. I didn't
sleep last night. I slept a few hours in
the daytime today. Looks like it's going
to be another one of those nights.
Pakistan is back to its dirty dirty
tricks. Here we have it. See, I told
you. I told you
within minutes of what I said we are
witnessing what's happening
here. Uh Luna is very upset and I
understand ma'am why you're upset all
Indian politicians are coward. Please
don't I don't think all Indian
politicians are coward. We have some
good good politicians. Please don't be
negative. I know it hurts that we were
forced to accept a ceasefire but the
ceasefire the Pakistanis have given us a
great gift. They violated it. End of
story, bro. Freezing hawk says drones in
Gujarat too. Look at that. Look at that.
These people cannot be trusted. These
people cannot be trusted. You have to
end their capacity for doing such things
in the future ever.
Ever. Now Deep Patel says what about
China's infrastructure in Paka Pakistan
occupied Kashmir. If India gets back the
territory, chances of maj major
escalation. Hey,
China, you want to play? Really? It It's
entirely up to China. Okay. Once we take
back Pok, let's say by tomorrow
morning, the ball is in China's court.
You want to what's the polite
word? What's the polite word? You want
to play? You want to play that game, do
you? You want to make a move?
Well, bring it on.
See China's infrastructure in P doesn't
belong to China. P is Indian territory.
And if they have any infrastructure in
in the territory, it is
illegitimate. They have not taken our
permission to build it. The moment we
take back, we retake the territory.
Everything on the territory is ours and
China better stay out of it. Otherwise,
China will face issues. We have seen the
quality of their of their weapons
systems, of their air defense systems,
of their radars, of their missiles. What
next? What's the quality of your
aircraft? What's the quality of your
soldiers? We'll see. It's not that easy.
The territory, the terrain in the
region, the P region is so
difficult. It is so rugged,
mountainous. It's not easy for China to
just walk in. They'll be wiped out. So,
it's not that
easy for China to do something.
So uh yeah I don't think there's a
chance of major escalation as long as we
make our move fast. If we take 7 days 10
days to take P then the Chinese can make
a move and do things and come in the
way. But if we are in PK by tomorrow
morning or in the next 72 hours that the
Chinese simply don't have the time to do
anything. So yeah there we go. There we
there we have it. There we have it. So
once more uh Nikil is saying Pakistan is
violating the ceasefire. Blackout at
Vishno Dvi, Shinagar, blackout in
Virospur and Patan court. They're
targeting temples. There are blasts
heard in
Shinagar. Okay, let's revisit this
question. VP says GD Vance said
yesterday that it's none of US's
business. It's none of America's
business this fight between India and
Pakistan and now the US claims efforts
behind the ceasefire. Why this 180°ree
turn? It's because the US is the most
powerful country in the world and they
can do whatever they want. It this is
what many people would call hypocrisy.
Yesterday you said this, today you've
done a 180°ree turn. That's what comes
with power. The ability ability to
change your trajectory based on your
whims and fancies and based on whatever
is convenient to you at any given point
in time. Right? So it should not be
surprising and you should not feel upset
about it. Don't take it personally.
That's what powerful nations do. And you
should aspire to make India a nation
that can also play that game. Okay. So
that that's how it is. I I I don't feel
betrayed by the US. No, they'll do that.
They'll do whatever suits them best as
they should and we should be in a
position to do whatever suits us best.
So we need to be more powerful. We have
to all work together in that direction.
That's what needs to
happen. Sergeant Skylands says, "Why
does Pakistan want to escalate? They
can't hold out for a week. It beats me
what goes on in those
minds. What goes on in these
minds? They had the the the most golden
of
opportunities 1 hour
ago, 2 hours ago once Donald Trump made
the announcement.
What they should have done is they
should have they should have religiously
observed the ceasefire for the next 3 to
6 months. And in the meanwhile, they
should have built everything back. Their
airports which were destroyed, they
should have built them back. Their
runways which were riddled with craters
and holes, they should have repaired
those runways. Whatever fighter planes
they had lost, they could have bought
more or begged more from China, right?
Whatever ammunition was depleted, they
could have bought from China or Turkey
or whatever. And in six months time they
should have started a new thing back
back to square one with India. That's
what a logical person a logical
terrorist nation would do. But they are
an illogical terrorist nation. Clearly
the ch the Pakistanis. Why are they
escalating? I just don't get
it. I just don't. Omar Abdullah is
saying there is no
ceasefire. The ceasefire is gone. It's
over. Air defense is activated in
Sinagar.
What sort of insanity is
this? The Pakistanis got their offramp,
right? We gave them the offramp. Donald
Trump gave them the offramp. Here's your
deescalation. Go back. Go back to where
you were. Take your time. Rebuild
everything and start then start
everything again from square one if you
want in 6 months time. But
no, this is madness. this sort of
insanity, it's it's dangerous for the
world and it's dangerous for us. Now,
enough of this. We need to deal with
them and and finish these these these
criminals
off. Oshima says, uh, such an attack
just hours after the declaration of a
ceasefire must mean some sort of
guarantee to no consequences by a higher
power, either the US or China or
otherwise. This is
suicide. Um, I'm not sure about that.
that that is a scenario we can certainly
consider and I don't think it's the case
but it is certainly something that makes
logical sense. I don't think the
Americans would have given the
Pakistanis an assurance that okay we
have created a ceasefire for you but you
are free to break it immediately then
why then then look I'll tell you why I
don't think it's the case because this
makes Donald Trump look like a fool it's
like a slap in the face of Donald Trump
by Pakistan what's happening right
now the Pakistanis were given their
offramp their their chance to rebuild in
6 months time and start leading India
again if they want, right? And look,
they slapped Donald Trump in the face
and made him look like an absolute fool.
Now we have to tell Donald Trump,
"Donald Trump, sir, the Pakistanis have
made you look like a fool. Please,
please, Donald Trump, you are the great
Donald Trump, the greatest man on the
world. Will you tolerate this
insult? Will you tolerate this insult,
Donald Trump?" That's what we need to
tell him. The Pakistanis seem to have
chosen suicide. I don't know what logic
is behind this. I don't know if their
brain actually processes things
logically. But I don't know. I don't
know. But Mclovin says what will be the
aftermath both both globally and
domestically once we are done with
Pakistan? Yeah. The aftermath the
Americans won't like it will be a much
different India. If we break po break
Pakistan just
imagine the change in the confidence
level of Indians they'll walk with their
chests out wherever they go in the world
in the world anywhere we have not had a
win like this for a thousand years
essentially you know a nation needs
victories we Indians have not tasted
victory in decades and years in
centuries 1947 was not a victory we were
given
so-called independence on British
terms. We did not win the independence.
The term was that you you cut your
country in half and put one piece here
and put one piece there. That's a that's
a loss. And we have swallowed that. We
are a nation of people who made these
painful compromises. This if it happens,
if we break Pakistan at whatever cost
and we finish this once and for all that
will put India on a whole different
trajectory, we will not be the same
again. The world won't be able to look
at us in the same way again. There'll be
an element of fear about India in the
future once this happens. That's why the
US doesn't want this to happen. That's
why the US wants a ceasefire and the
Pakistanis have violated
it. Here we go. India retaliates with
loitering munitions to Pakistan's
provocation. We are once again going up
the escalation
ladder.
Madness. Madness. Explosions heard
across Trinagar. This is
insanity. In real time, we are
witnessing the end of the ceasefire and
the resumption of
warfare. I just don't understand these
people. This is this is this is suicide.
Like Ashima was saying just
now. Uh Luffy says when will we have a
border with Iran? Sooner or later I
think it'll be uh it'll take more time.
Right now the ideal situation scenario
for us is that by tomorrow morning we
are in Tok and by the end of 10 days
Pakistan is in three three four
different pieces. Chasan is independent
which means Balojasthan has a border
with Iran. Now we don't want to occupy
Balojasthan at this point in time. It's
too early for that. We have to handhold
them back to a proper status which may
take a few decades maybe two three
decades and then we can see about think
about in reintegration into our
territory we should not make the people
of Bjasan feel like you know so we've
got our independence and but we were
reabsorbed by India and now India is the
occupied we should not make them feel
that way so the ideal scenario is the
balkcanization of Pakistan now blackout
in Rajasthan Jal mayor
Patan quote Vishno Dvi Cargill Udampur
my god my god in real time we are
witnessing the unraveling of Donald
Trump's ceasefire this is a major insult
to Donald Trump this is a slap in the
face of Donald Trump by Pakistan not by
India I think Donald Trump should
personally take action against Pakistan
now okay
um what else do we
Swapnil Muanti says, "Will this victory
be greater than the Bangladesh
liberation?" Look, we haven't tasted
victory yet. Right now, there is no
victory. But if it happens, if we even
if we don't break up Pakistan, even if
we just take back even some portion of
PK, it'll be a huge victory. And the
long-term consequences of that will, I
promise you, be the dismantling of
Pakistan. And when that happens, it will
be the biggest victory of all, much
bigger than
71. So it's going to be a process. It's
going to be a series of steps. The
Pakistanis have dragged us back into
war. My goodness, I cannot understand
the mentality of these
people. I just don't understand these
people. They had the most golden of
chances. Within
hours, they have destroyed it.
Nilles says, "I was I had lost hope and
I was sad, but your talk brought up my
hopes and ceasefire violated." Look, I I
appreciate that what you're saying. What
has brought up the hopes is that the
Pakistanis violated the ceasefire and I
thought it would happen and that's why I
I said those things. So there you have
it. It's it's done. Um so my point is my
friends, please don't be negative.
Please don't be pessimistic. Always be
optimistic in life. Always be optimistic
and please remember what we are capable
of. what our potential is and now we are
turning that potential energy into
kinetic energy. It's happening. Please
be positive. Always be
positive.
[Music]
Uh okay. Saraj says, "Are we losing the
information warfare dimension? Are we
are we losing that? How was Pakistan
able to post pro park articles in major
media platforms?" Yeah, because that's a
good question. If you see the western
media h whether it's BBC, whether it's
the New York Times, whether it's the
Washington Post, whether it is US vasals
and their media outlets like Luffy of
France, whether it is the Chavel,
whether it is in the eastern world,
Japanese or other publications, you will
see they consistently have this virulent
anti-India stance. Whenever they publish
something about India, it's going to be
a negative publication. It's going to be
it's going to the the approach towards
India is going to be negative, right?
Why is it that especially the UK
Guardian, BBC and so on, all these US
vasals. Why is it like that? It's
because of the legacy of the first cold
war where India had chosen to be on the
side of the USSR and Pakistan was on the
side of the West. So from their
perspective, India was their enemy. It
was part of the adversaries camp and
that's why they had to demonize India.
That's why they were okay with funding
and financing Pakistani terrorism
against our
citizens. So that approach that
mentality that mindset that the western
media has see the western media is a
force amplifier. If you want to bomb a
country 6 months down the line you start
the negative coverage from today so that
the whole public is mentally conditioned
to believe that this country is is is
bad. Like when the Ukraine war happened,
the special military operation in
February 2022, India refused to
participate in Western sanctions against
Russia and India doubled down on buying
more Russian oil. And what was the
consequence of that? every single
disposable minion the West had, every
so-called analyst, every single uh
geopolitical analyst, every single think
tank that they had, Rand Corporation,
every Rand Corporation member, every
publication, they all started putting
out a barrage of anti-India
content. Right? So if you do that for 6
months, 1 year, 2 years, then the whole
western public population will be
conditioned to look at India in a
negative light. And they've always done
that. You know, they've portrayed India
as a very backward as a country with a
very backward culture. We are
non-western, right? We are a
polytheistic culture. We are a proud
polytheistic culture. The oldest culture
that that exists in the world. And they
hate that. They have they hate that they
have not been able to break us. and
they're still trying to break us, right?
Uh so that coverage is always going to
be negative. So that's why it's so easy
for Pakistan to put its point forward in
the western media. See what the west
typically does when they want to write
anti-India articles, whether it's the
BBC, whether it's the Guardian, whether
it is uh the Washington Post, they will
hire
Indians to write those articles.
And there are lots of Indians who are
willing to to sell their their
motherland for a few dollars, right? So
they will hire Indians to write those
articles. And similarly, they will have
lots of Pakistanis on their
payroll. So it's a piece of cake to
write anti-India and pro Pakistan
articles. It's going to happen, you
know, like clockwork. It's going to
happen on autopilot.
So that's why we end up using the losing
the information warfare because the
media is controlled by the west. All the
social media platforms are controlled by
the west. They owned by the west. We
have not bothered to create anything. We
don't have our version of the BBC or CNN
or Al Jazzer or anything. We have not
just not bothered with these things. We
simply don't care. Apparently the
government has all the opportunity to do
that in the past 10 years. That's a
failure. Past 11 years failure. But I
appreciate what they've done with this
war. So ceasefire violations everywhere.
Okay, wonderful. Good job
Pakistan. They just says they will still
blame India that India did not follow
the ceasefire and they'll try to paint
us as the villain. So they just is very
right. The Pakistanis now will claim
that we have violated the ceasefire.
That's what they're going to they're
going to do. They're going to try and
portray us as the aggressor. Trump has
egg on his face is what is being said
over here on on the screen. All right.
All right. What next? What other things
do we have? Dongarin Johan says our
leaders are naive. See our leaders
historically have been super naive
geopolitically. No understanding of the
concept of the national interest. What
is India's national interest? That is
the first thing you have to know to be
able to navigate the geopolitical world.
Let's say you are a complete novice as a
leader. You have been elected from some
some you know backwater but you became
the prime minister hypothetically and
you have no understanding of the world.
You know that there's a country called
the US, there's a country called this
that but you don't know anything about
them. But that's okay. As long as you
know what your national interest is, you
can navigate everything just by
following the guidelines of the national
interest. But we have had leaders who
did not even know what the national
interest
was. Should I name them? We all know who
I name, right? The great magnificent Mr.
So and so and so on. Not not only that,
Mr. So and so many others. So they were
naive. Now I I'll assure you of one
thing. Mr. Modi isn't naive. Mr. Modi
isn't kn. So that is a caveat I'll put.
Dungaran is absolutely right.
Historically our leaders have been
naive. And today if you look at all the
political leaders I think many of them
would not have a good understanding of
geopolitics but I would say Mr. Modi is
not naive not naive at all. Noel says
ceasefire broken. Yeah it's broken.
Ceasefire is broken. Uh Kiadi the Chad
says if Baljasthan becomes independent
can it become anti-Indian just like
Bangladesh even after India is helping
them in their independence. It all
depends on us. In 1971, Bangladesh
should have been reabsorbed into India.
Okay. Let's say for whatever reason, we
did not reabsorb Bangladesh into India.
Then we should have had ensured that
whatever Bangladesh government comes to
power, it should be a pro-India
government and we should protect it. But
we took our hands off Bangladesh. So
Bangladesh went back in the radical
direction. And today they are so
strongly uh indoctrinated mentally
mentally the people of Bangladesh most
of them against India. They're just like
Pakistan. Bangladesh has become East
Pakistan. It is our failure. We did not.
We just let the nation go. We should
have exerted complete control over the
nation while allowing it to remain
independent. What's wrong with that?
That's what all great powers do. But we
did not behave like a great power. Now
in the future, if Balojasthan becomes
independent, we should handhold the
country. We should appoint ourselves,
declare ourselves as the
protector of Bangladesh. we should
declare of of of Balojasthan. We should
declare that Balojasthan is an Indian
protectorate and we will take care of
you and that's the approach we should
have going forward and that approach
should last the next few
decades and we should guide them about
everything they are supposed to do and
in what way they're supposed to do
without becoming overbearing and without
trying to interfere too much in their
their lives. That's what you do. That
way it will never become
anti-India. But we failed when it comes
to Bangladesh. We just let it go, right?
That's the
failure.
Okay. Okay. Good question by Rada. Now
that Pakistan has violated the
ceasefire, will America again try to
mediate or will it just step back
now? Uh, that's a good question. Will
Trump again try to come in the way? I
think now it's a it's it's it's gone too
far. It's gone too far. Yeah. But who
knows? Trump is right now essentially
humiliated. He has been slapped in the
face. He has egg on his face like this
channel is saying. Yeah. So I don't I
would recommend to Shri Donald Trump G
that now stay out of it and punish
Pakistan. Samat says but why did Trump
stop us? I said and I've been saying the
past few days that the US has given
divorce papers to the temporary nation.
So why did Trump save Pakistan now?
Good question. The the US doesn't want
to have Pakistan as their Wasar anymore,
but they still want Pakistan's nuisance
value visav India and they still want to
be able to give Pakistan these little
gifts from like IMF if no loans and so
on. So that Pakistan also plays their
game. So Pakistan is now definitely
looking to China as their big daddy and
that is very clear from the fact that
they have been saying openly that they
they were doing terrorism on on the US's
behest. So that's divorce. But the
Americans still want some control over
Pakistan and as long as dollars are
coming in, the Pakistanis
will do what the Americans tell them as
long as the dollars come in. So Trump
wants Pakistan to still have some
leverage value over India. It should it
should still function as some form of
leverage over India and that's why he's
doing it. So Pakistan is now going to be
a Chinese but they will still keep on
fishing for American money and that way
America can control Pakistan to some
extent. keep on controlling unless China
is able to give way more money to
Pakistan than the US can. In that case,
Pakistan will stop caring about the US.
So it will all depend on what on the on
the quantum of dollars that is flowing
in to Pakistan in from which direction
it is flowing in. But the US knows how
to play these games. So that's why it's
happening the the what's happening is
happening. Okay. Rupali says
something wipe
out West
India. I don't know. Look, you can be
fatalistic, you can be negative or you
can be positive. So don't cry like that.
Don't be so negative. I I I don't know
how to I have not read the Bhavvisha
Puran and I'm not sure there is any
mention of Pakistan in the Bhaves Puran.
If there is then I don't know about it.
But look, let's not be uh fatalistic and
negative. Let us be more optimistic.
Let's be positive. Look, the Pakistanis
have given us this big gift today. Big
gift. Let's use it. Let us use it.
Amrits are good god what's
happening. Ravi uh sorry Rajiv says why
does India not use DD news to put forth
their national interests in narrative? I
I don't know why we don't do it. Diddy
news is a great asset to have turned it
into a global
behemoth
right I just I don't know looks like
there is no vision big vision or big big
ambition to do this it can be
done says my confidence is crazy high
and I haven't felt more alive than in
the past 78 72 hours yeah that's what
happens when your nation wins we still
haven't won the victory the victory will
be when we change the lines on the map
but we have hit Pakistan like anything
the past 72 hours we have destroyed the
spectre of their nuclear blackmail we
have showed that it's hollow but that's
not enough but yeah nothing unifies and
unites the nation better than winning
and victory and the nation needs more of
this so that's why I I would say that
it's time to it's time to do what needs
to be done with Pakistan then India will
never be the same again never that
inferiority complex in Indian it may
disappear to some
extent. Gur Gur Sebak says we we've got
the world's bravest community on our
side. Remember we are all brave people.
I I know what he's talking about. He's
talking about the sick people.
Absolutely. We are proud of the sick and
we are proud of everyone who fights in
our armed forces. So absolutely
absolutely. Uh Shir Sai Toa says news
has come that Pakistan has violated the
ceasefire. The Kashmir CM has confirmed
it. What will be Trump's reaction now? I
would recommend to Mr. Donald Trump that
you should be very
angry. The you gave Pakistan the
ultimate
gift, the gift that would ensure
Pakistan's survival. And they have
chosen to spit on your face. They've
chosen to slap you in the face. They
have insulted you, Mr. Donald Trump by
by rejecting your ceasefire. They are
people who cannot be trusted. They have
stabbed you in the back, Mr. Donald
Trump. Please either punish them
yourself or leave them to our
mercy and let us finish what we said. Oh
my goodness. Ah, air defense systems all
over the place. Here we go. Nothing has
changed. Nothing has changed.
Pratam says, "Can Pakistan change the
narrative and make it look like India
has violated the ceasefire?" I suppose
that's the first thing there going to
do. Pakistan has a gift for lying. They
will always
lie. But now we should not care anymore.
Okay? See, we in India have this habit
of trying to prove that we are right.
We'll come up with these intelligence
dosier and and and information dumps and
all the proof and all the evidence and
we'll try to convince the world. See, we
are right
because I say to hell with
it. We know who's done what and that's
enough. That's good enough for us. Why
do we have to prove to the world and
convince the world that we are
right? We have to operate from a
position of strength now. We gave them
the chance and we we saw that they have
violated the ceasefire. Now we don't
have to prove anything to anyone. They
have violated the ceasefire. We're going
to punish them now. And that's how it
should be. Please grow some
confidence. Stop trying to convince the
world that you are right. You should not
have that need inside you that we have
to demonstrate, we have to prove and we
have to show the world that see we are
right. Please agree with us. We should
say to hell with you. We are right. We
are a righteous nation. We are not a
nation of terrorists. And we will do
what is right. And we will punish the
terrorists whether you like it or not.
And you the west have been funding and
financing terrorism. So this is the end
of that. That's what we need to
do. Um Sam Kosh says this isn't going to
stop sooner. No, no, no. It's not it's
not stopping now. It's it's gone back to
to where it was last night.
Summer says again CFBs like heavy
shelling in RSpura happening again with
BSF cleared to act said by CM of JNK
saying that there is no ceasefire. The
ceasefire is over. Blackout in Cargill,
blackout in Shinagar, Patan Court, Westo
Devi, Udampur, Firospur, Patan Court,
Bar. India is retaliating with loitering
munitions. Pakistan is back to its dirty
tricks. There we have it. The ceasefire
is over. CM Omar is saying what about
the ceasefire? Explosions have been
heard all across Trinagar. This is
unforgivable.
Unforgivable. Vidy Manar says, "Are we
ser seriously a sovereign nation? Please
answer with on point point black blank
honesty. I doubt after what the US could
do to us today. How is Israel sovereign
then? What about our
interest?" Yes, we are sovereign. That's
why we were able to bring Pakistan to
its knees and that's now what's going to
happen. But the question you're asking
is a good question. And let's understand
the perspective. Sovereignty is
relative. We have see first of all let's
let's do it from first principles which
means let's define what it means to be a
sovereign nation. To be a sovereign
nation you need certain conditions to be
fulfilled. Firstly you need to have
complete control over who enters and
exits your country which we do. Second
which we mostly do. Secondly, you need
to have complete control over your
borders. Your borders should be
inviable, which we do mostly once again.
Okay. Thirdly, you need to have complete
control over your economy, which means
you need to have your own reserve bank,
central bank, and you need to have your
own currency which you control that we
do, right? And lastly, you need to have
complete control over the policies that
are implemented in your country, which
once again we do. So from the definition
of from this definition and these
conditions we are a sovereign country.
We have some issues of infiltration and
all but we are entirely capable of
ending that like this if you want. So we
are a sovereign country but there is a
power differential. The
US is way more powerful than us and they
can arm twist us and make us do things
that are not in our interests. It
doesn't mean we are not sovereign. It
means we are not powerful enough to to
say no to the US. It is not a violation
of sovereignty. What what what would
cons constitute a violation of
sovereignty by the US towards India?
Either taking some of our territory or
forcing us to accept a US military base
on our soil or um other kinds of
violations like economic violations like
you know uh destroying the the the the
Indian currency or forcing us to adopt
certain policies that are not in our
interests you know changing our laws and
all that that doesn't happen. So we are
sovereign from that from that
perspective. But we would like to be
more powerful. See what you're actually
asking is are we why are we not powerful
enough to say no to the US like what
Russia can do. So we need to work
towards that. But we are definitely
sovereign. We are one of the I've always
said we there are four sovereign nations
right the US, Russia, China, India. Four
sovereign nations. Let me modify that
statement. There are five sovereign
nations in the world. There's one more
that I have not mentioned before and I
was not right to not mention it. The
fifth sovereign nation is
Israel. It
is. Yeah, it is. And uh that's a whole
different matter and that's not for
today's discussion. But yeah, the
ceasefire has been destroyed by
Pakistan. Ceasefire broken. See, Bhavik
is is
confirming. Gurroit says love the brains
of Pakistan. I just don't get it. Air
defense guns have been activated.
Complete background blackout in Pokran.
Eight Pakistani drones
spotted. What is wrong with these
people? I just don't get it.
Uh Pragal Chandelia says, "What are the
possible reactions from the US to the
ceasefire violation?" The most obvious
reaction, logical reaction should be to
throw Pakistan to the wolves and tell
India do whatever you want now or
otherwise they can try and rebroker the
ceasefire which would be really stupid.
So I think now that the ceasefire is
broken if they want to rebroken the
ceasefire it'll take some time for that
that to happen maybe 24 to 48 hours
maybe 12 to 24 hours that gives us a
window of opportunity.
Now it's not enough to to send missiles
as guests to Pakistan to Rahul Pindi to
whatever air bases they have. Now it is
time to send our guests with armor into
Pakistan occupied Kashmir until we have
until morning I guess to do that. Enough
is enough
both. Aditi says if Pakistan balconizes
into four, won't it be difficult to deal
with it with these newborn Islamic
nations? They may be thankful at the
beginning but then later they'll
remember that they are people of the
book. Look, it all depends on how we
deal with it. If we handhold these
nations in a certain
way and we declare these nations to be
our protectorates and we give them aid,
we give them guidance. We help them set
up their institutions, judiciary,
parliament, uh education system, this
that we give them aid from our own
coffers. If we do all that, then they'll
be very thankful to us. So then we can
guide them in the right direction.
Obviously a lot of the population sadly
is going to be radicalized. So we're
going to have to deal with it very
judiciously very properly. But it's
feasible if we make the same mistakes
that we made with Bangladesh that after
the nation was given independence we
just let it go and do whatever it wants
then we will have the same situation
again. Then somebody else will be able
to come into the region and influence
these nations more than we can influence
them. So we need to have a proper clear
path and plan from day zero not from day
one from day zero which means right now.
If we do it right then we will be the
nation that will expand its influence in
the subcontinent and guide these people
back to mother India which needs to
happen eventually.
Right. Chiag says their arm is copying
India to save face. If they back down,
they risk they being dethroned. Isn't
deescalation nearly impossible? Because
because of a robust air defense, you
know, that's possibly the logic behind
what they're doing because they have
been humiliated. The Pakistani army, the
Pakistani military has been humiliated
and the whole aam of Pakistan. The
people of Pakistan have seen this with
their own eyes. What India has done to
the Pakistan military. India has not
struck at Pakistan civilians. Pakistani
civilians I saw they're standing and
watching the missiles rain down on
Pakistani air bases and they're filming
it. They knew they will not be touched.
You see this is the thing about India.
India India has ethics. We don't touch
civilians. All the explosions all the
blasts were on Pakistani military ex
installations and the civilians could
stand and watch that and film that
without being afraid. Now when it comes
to Pakistani military activity against
India h that they have been doing our
civilians are afraid because they only
target civilians. That is the difference
between a civilized nation and the
barbaric nation. We will only target
their terrorist camps their terrorist
infrastructure and then we'll target the
military which is an honorable thing to
do. The fight should be between two
militaries. You should never target
civilians and that is not in part of our
culture to target civilians, men, women,
children. So that's why the Pakistani
civilians aren't scared. But our
civilians, they are frightened when the
Pakistanis start shelling or or sending
drones because they are trying to hit
civilian areas. Shameless people. This
this bunch of criminals needs to be
excised from the world. Okay. There are
drones above Kutch in Gujarat.
So the point is they are the military of
Pakistan has been humiliated. The entire
population of Pakistan has seen that
that they are important. They are
helpless against India. Which means that
there is there is now going to be a
sentiment to remove these people because
they're useless and they bring nothing
of value to the to the table for the
people of Pakistan. So that's why the
military is in a tough spot today. Even
if there's a ceasefire, they they feel
like they have they have been
humiliated. They've lost faith and they
need to do something to avenge the what
India has done. So they're starting this
nonsense again. They're starting this
nonsense
again and we have this shockingly robust
air defense that they can't penetrate.
So I wonder what they're going to try
now. Yeah, but that's where we go. T
Aaral says, "Has Pakistan violated the
ceasefire?" It has. Absolutely.
Absolutely it has violated ceasefire.
Half of India, Western India around the
border regions is blacked out right now.
Shi Pratab says will Pakistan go for
nukes if we take back our P or no I
don't think they will dare to to
escalate to nukes if we take back
P what we need to do is we need to do it
very rapidly before the sun comes out we
should be in control of P if we do that
they won't have the time to react
especially if we keep them busy with air
strikes with missile strikes and drone
strikes at the same time and we have
other weapons battlefield weapons that
can sanitize a wide area before we enter
it. So you know and and I don't think
the Pakistanis will dare use nukes
because the moment they cross that
threshold there won't be any planes out
of Pakist out of Lahore or Karachi or
Ral Pendi to London there won't be any
planes left to go anywhere they will
evaporate the Pakistani military I don't
think they will do
that if we so it depends on the
calibration of our attack of our advance
if we simply take back very quickly P
Okay, then they'll not be not have the
time to to to react to that and then we
can simply put a pause the pulse pause
war and then you defend P okay from
Pakistan it's no longer P okay it's now
Jammu and Kashmir that's what needs to
happen Amitab says is it possible that
Pakistan is breaking this ceasefire on
purpose as said by their previous master
US to help the US form military camps to
counter China and India on Pakistan
insider
It doesn't make a lot of sense. If they
really need that sort of help, then let
us take over Pakistan and we will
organize the military camp. The US wants
on that part of the territory. How about
that? Yeah, we can offer the US a deal.
Um, it doesn't really make sense. I
think Pakistan is simply a the military
is simply a set of criminals are simply
a set of barbarians who have no value
for human life who who simply don't
value the lives of their people of their
citizens and they use their citizens and
their country as cannon foder and and
and sheep to be to be exploited. It's so
sad and they have brainwashed the people
into believing that they are their
saviors. So I don't think it's it's it's
the case but it's an interesting
scenario that you brought up and I'm I'm
glad that people think about various
scenarios in this
manner.
Hershit okay was it a mind game by India
agreeing to ceasefire knowing that
Pakistan won't follow thus gaining
international support and a moral upper
hand for a full-fledged war. No I think
it wasn't a mind game. I think that
India knew that if Donald Trump asks us
for a ceasefire, we can't say no to him.
Okay, we need Mr. Trump on our side.
He's not a bad person. He's a good
person. He overall is a friend of India
as far as a friend can exist in
geopolitics. And of course, we knew that
Pakistan will violate the
ceasefire. But will we gain
international support now is the
question because the western media will
I promise you paint this as something
that maybe we have done. Maybe Pakistan
tried to do a ceasefire but India broke
the ceasefire. They may put the blame on
India. The media game is very dirty. So
uh I don't think it's a mind game. India
look we were trying to give them an
offramp from day one. From day one of
operation Sindur it's no longer
operation sindur now it's India Pakistan
war. But from day one of operation
Sindor we said okay we did this now we
are done. We have punished the
terrorists. Now we want to stop. But the
Pakistanis hit back. Then we again hit
back. Then we said, "Let's stop now."
Okay, you don't get to save your face,
but we're willing to stop. So, we gave
them an an offramp, an
outlet, you know, every single
time. And now, Donald Trump gave them an
off-ramp. And these
people have blown it. So, it's it's just
madness. Madness.
Um who who who says there are past
records of Pakistanis using Nepal to
spread terrorism and potentially setting
up safe camps and secret bases there.
Could such tactics be used near the end
of Pakistan and how can it affect
Nepal? Um it's it's happened in the past
that Pakistanis have had a presence in
Nepal. Maybe most likely not with the
actual knowledge and all that of the
Nepales government possibly. Yeah. uh
and Pakistan is a threat to Nepal. In
the in the Helgam attack, one Nepalese
citizen very sadly was killed by the
Pakistanis because he was a Hindu,
right? So Nepal and India have to be
united in this matter and uh um they
will possibly try to use Pakistan to
spread terrorism and and destabilize
India. Sorry, they'll use Nepal to
destabilize India and spread terror. So
Nepal should not allow these terrorists
to use Nepalese territory, sacred
territory of the Himalayan region of of
the Thai region of Nepal to be used for
such disgusting nefarious anti- inhuman
purposes and we should work with Nepal
coord coordinate with Nepal to ensure
that this doesn't happen. But yeah, if
it's if it's possible for them, they
would definitely try and do that. They
will want to do that.
Surya Pawan says if India wins the war,
can Pakistan become an autonomous region
within India with a separate
constitution like the various republics
of Russia, Saka and so on so forth with
restricting people migrating from
autonomous region. uh that's definitely
a scenario that can be considered but I
think the safest scenario is that we
give independence to the various nations
Balojasthan Sinduh
uh Khibar Pakuma goes back to
Afghanistan and PJK and Gilgit Baltistan
returns to India and Punjab can remain
West Punjab or whatever I think that's
the best scen way of doing it and the
reason for this is that the Pakistani
education system and the military and
all that they have radicalized their
people very badly to such an extent that
most Pakistani citizens despite being
individually good people they all are
taught to hate India and to hate Hindus
and you can't have that population
merging with India now if you make it an
autonomous region with India but with a
separate constitution but you don't
allow the people to to mingle with India
to migrate within India and so on it
kind of defeats the purpose right then
the west and the world can portray that
as the occupation of those regions by
India as a foreign power. They can
portray it like that. We don't want that
to happen. So it's an interesting um
it's an interesting arrangement that
you're proposing but you have to look at
the pros and cons. And the biggest con
is that if we do it this way then our
enemies or adversaries of we don't of
which we have plenty they will portray
us as occupiers.
they're occupying Muslim lands or
something, you know, we don't want to be
in that scenario,
right? Push Mahan Singh says, "Can we
say that our air defense system has
proven to be stronger and better than
the Iron Dome system?"
100%. The Iron Dome. Okay, we haven't
opened the map today. Let me open the
map and show you something.
H Let me show you something. Let's Let's
go to the map. Let's uh where is map is
here. So let's look at Israel. Israel is
this small country H which is defended
by the Iron Dome system. Uh what's the
end to end distance measurement of
Israel? It's about 400
kilometers. So 400 km and this uh to
this is 200. So let's say it's about 800
9 let's say a thousand square
kilometers. Okay that's the patch of
land Israel has to defend. Now when it
comes to India we have millions of
square kilometers. The entire western
border with Pakistan is if you just take
a straight line from here to to here
let's say it's 1500
kilometers and we have to defend at
least 100 km or 200 km inside.
So
1,500 times 100 it's like 30 3 million.
How much? What is the thing? One second.
Okay. Give me a second. Um
1,500 1500
* 200 is 3 million square kilmters at
least that we are defending.
Hm. When we are defending this this
territory from all kinds of of threats,
including cruise missiles, including um
including uh long range rockets,
including ballistic missiles, including
drones of various kinds, loitering
drones, low-flying drones, all kinds of
things. And we have defended this entire
terrain territory spotlessly.
You simply can't compare what we have
achieved with what the Israelis are
doing. I have the greatest of respect
for Israel and the technology. But our
air defense is superior to Israel. My
god, can you believe it? This is a great
question that pushing asked. What we
have witnessed the past 3 days is the
superiority of our air defense system to
to Israel. There's no comparison
today. There's no comparison. I'm sure
if Israel is given that sort of
territory 3 million square kilometers to
defend in a few years they may be able
to do that to develop the technology and
the capacity to do that. They certainly
are capable of doing that but they don't
need to. So if we compare the two we are
way ahead and a lot of that is atman the
Akash SAM system surfaceto-air missile
system is indigenous. My god what a
resounding success it has been. The
Barak system is also indigenous but it's
Indo-Israeli. It's a joint
development. And the Barak system is
used to defend our warships also from
threats. The Barak system is so potent
it can take out the bramos. It can
defend a ship from the Brahmos. So our
warships have the cure as well as the
threat on the same ship. We have the
Brahmos and we also have the Barak. And
the barak can be used on land also to
defend
territory. Amazing. I I I don't
know, you know, I really need to express
my gratitude and my pride in our
engineers and scientists who have
developed all these systems and also the
operators that is the Indian military,
the air defense uh personnel. incredible
job. We We need to celebrate these
heroes. You have no idea what they've
achieved the past 72 hours and now
they're going to do some more. Now
they're going to have to do more because
the Pakistanis have violated the
ceasefire. So incredible performance by
by India when it comes to air
defense. Shivam says Omar Abdullah has
tweeted that there is no ceasefire. The
air defense units in the middle of
Shinagar just opened up.
Sirana. Yes, absolutely. It's it's time
now. We got to punish them. We've got to
punish
them. Um Karma Dash says, "You are
unaware that war has started again." So
I have a TV screen behind this lens. You
see this lens here? Behind the lens, I
have a TV screen on the wall and I know
exactly what's happening. Pakistan has
violated the ceasefire. Understanding
air raid sirens across Gujarat now.
Yeah.
Then there are blasts in Shinagar. The
ceasefire is gone. The war has started
again. Can't blame us anymore if it if
it goes back to war. If it goes back to
war. It is going back to war. Uh Bharav
says from Twitter, when will the MEA do
their conference? Now at an appropriate
time. There is going to be no hastiness
in doing the next press conference.
We're going to wait for the situation to
evolve and maybe in the morning or maybe
afternoon tomorrow at an appropriate
time. We will uh have the MEA doing its
next press
conference.
Um okay. So I've already taken this.
Eizen is asking why did the IMF agree to
give this loan or whatever it is to
Pakistan for the 24th time despite the
situation? Because the US wants to have
some leverage over Pakistan and the best
leverage is money money and Donald
Trump, Mr. Trump understands money,
money, money. Uh what if Pakistan uses
MIRV missile for nucing India? Listen,
let's not
discuss they possibly may have some MIRV
kind of
thing. The point is this very simple. If
they use, if they succeed in detonating
a nuclear weapon on Indian territory
anywhere, it is the end of the world for
Pakistan. We will in that case absorb
some
loss, but Pakistan will cease to exist.
It's not going to be mutually assured
destruction. It's going to be one-sided.
We will survive. We will continue. But
they will be finished. End of story for
Pakistan. If they if they go down the
nuclear route, let me tell
Pakistan, there will be no planes out of
Lahore to London. There'll be nothing
out of Lahore or Islamabad or Karachi or
wherever. It's over. Don't you even
think about it. Don't you even think
about
it. Okay. Vishal says, "What if Trump
and Mr. Modi are what if they're playing
four-dimensional chess? both have some
kind of agreement and all this is to
sway other countries in support of
India. Look, that's
speculation. It is certainly uh
possible, feasible within the realm of
it. It certainly belongs in the realm of
possibility, but it's speculation. So, I
don't know. It's possible. Maybe there's
a small possibility, small probability
of this being true, but I'm not sure
about that.
So, yeah. Next. Sita says, "Is this a
sign of a revolt in the Pakistani army
with the new attacks on our LOC? Maybe
the Pakistani military wants to dislodge
Aim Munir from power and then they can
blame this on Aim Mun. But if it ends up
if it ends up causing the complete
destruction of Pakistan and what's the
point so I don't know it's crazy. So
once again we have more confirmations
that ceasefire has been violated. Rohan
is thank very nicely telling us this. So
thank you Rohan. They just is
asking is Imran Khan dead? So I'm
hearing some rumors on on social media
that Imran Khan apparently is has died
but we don't have confirmation of that.
Yeah. So there we have it. I don't know.
Simei is saying terrorist attacks are
happening now. Okay. I haven't seen that
on the screen. I have only one TV
channel on but uh okay. So in that case
it's it's very clear that the ceasefire
is off and war is declared by Pakistan.
Okay, let's see. Uh, yeah, ceasefire is
is violated. It's done. It's finished.
No more no more ceasefire. Uh, I don't
know how to read this. I have never
learned the serillic script. So,
ceasefire is being violated constantly.
Will it affect US's credibility more and
China can make its propaganda more
solid? Oh, this will affect the
credibility of Donald J.
Trump. Mr. Trump made
this smug tweet. Where the tweet? Where
is the tweet? Let me let me go back to
Twitter. What's the tweet that he put
out? Donald Trump. Here it is. Let's
let's put that on the
screen. Very smug tweet by the US
president, Mr. Donald J. Trump. After a
long night of talks mediated by the
great United States and the great
president, I am pleased to announce that
the errant school boys India and
Pakistan have agreed to a full and
immediate ceasefire. Congratulations for
both countries on using common sense and
great intelligence. Thank you for your
attention. Class
dismissed. Is that so, Mr. Donald Trump?
Is class dismissed? The Pakistanis have
slapped you in your face, Donald Trump.
You need to punish them. You need to
take this personally, President Trump.
We have the greatest of respect for you,
but the Pakistanis have disrespected
you, President Trump. You've got to make
them pay for this. It otherwise it will
affect your
credibility. So there we have
it. Okay. Priya Prianjan says ceasefire
violation by Pakistan. Does it confirm
that Pakistan is a Banana Republic? It
confirms that Pakistan cannot be
trusted. It can't be trusted by India.
It can't be trusted by the United
States. It can't be trusted by anybody.
The Pakistanis have dug their own
grave. I don't know what's actually
happening on on the front lines now, but
the media is reporting what it's
reporting. Uh Munir openly defies Trump.
Government holds Pakistan accountable.
Okay, let's see about that. Air defense
guns are activated. India strikes
Pakistani drones over Sinagar.
All right. Rahul liar says, "Will the
Balojasthan independence movement at
present succeed? It all depends on what
happens in the next 24 to 48 to 70 72
hours." Uh, yeah, it can succeed. Now,
so Goo says, "So, it's now considered to
be an act of war." Yes, it is an act of
war. In enough of this, Swapnil says,
"Why do you call Pakistan an artificial
state with no identity or culture of its
own?" Good question. Let me this gives
me an opportunity to explain this and
and unpack this. So, I appreciate this.
by swap. Why do I call Pakistan an
artificial state? See, in 1947, Pakistan
was created by partitioning India. If
you look back at the history of India,
which goes back, if you look at the
archaeological record, at least 10,000
years, the oldest sites of the Sarasatu
civilization of that period are 9 and a
half thousand years old. And so India
has existed continuously as as a
continuously existing culture and
civilization for about 10,000 years,
right? And much of the STANU region was
in what is today Pakistan. So that is
our territory. That's our ancestral
territory. If you are a person whose
ancestry is from northern or western
India whether it's Kashmir Afghanistan
or whether it is Punjab whether it's
Hana whether it's Rajasthan Gujarat you
Maharashtra or Sind whatever you're
going to have ancestors who lived in
Syasindu you're going to have ancestors
who live in Pakist what is now Pakistan
it is our ancestor land it is a sacred
land and it's been taken over by these
terrorists so it was India was
partitioned undemocratically
The people of India from from that time
our grandparents and great-grandparents
were not given the opportunity to decide
whether they accept the partition or
not. It was imposed upon us. It was
forced upon us. So an artificial nation
was created. That's why I say Pakistan
is an artificial nation. It was created
by foreign forces. But they used proxies
like Jana and Gandhi and Neu and all
that who all accepted that okay the
partition is okay.
But were they the legitimate authorities
to accept on behalf of the entire
civilization? They were not. So it was
created for the to serve the
geopolitical interests of of Britain.
And the only identity of that Pakistan
has is that we are all Muslims and the
only real identity they have is that we
reject our ancestral culture. So we are
fishing for a new culture somewhere. Oh,
maybe we were Arabs.
and tur. So they are looking for daddies
outside of our geography when they're
all our people. So it has no identity of
its own. If you look at Turkey, what's
their identity? We are Turks. We speak
the Turkish language. Our ancestors were
from Yeah, there. That's a long story.
But if you here's the right way to see
it. Take Turkey as an example. If you
take religion out of the equation as a
factor, then they still have a distinct
Turkish culture and language, right?
It's distinctly Turkish and the both the
culture and the language. If you look at
Egypt, if you take away the the
religion, then they have the Arabic
language, which is kind of a problem
because it's not their ancestral
language. And the culture is also gone.
The Egyptian culture is gone. So that's
problem. uh but if you look at Pakistan
comparing it with Turkey if you remove
the culture the religion out of Pakistan
then their language is Indian and all
their customs and culture also are
Indian and their blood is Indian so
their entire
identity is in denying who they really
are and they try to ape foreign cultures
they try to make Turkish culture their
own earlier they used to make Arabic
culture their own now the Arabs don't
like Pakistani so now they're trying to
become Turks so that's The thing about
Pakistan it's it's terrible you know Mr.
ads it says 100% Turkish Turkish blood
sar oh man what happened
now okay I don't know about that I'm
seeing it all over social media all over
Indian media
uh ceasefire violated I don't know where
you're saying where you're seeing that I
don't think the army is making any
statements right now I don't think the
army is going to make statements as a
knee-jerk
reaction government said ceasefire is
over ceasefire
violated my god God, what is happening?
What is happening? What is happening?
Pakist Pakistani media already announced
this planned attack by Pakistan 3 hours
ago. It was surfacing like now. It has
attacked Udampur, Lal Choke and drones
everywhere, blackouts
everywhere. Oh man. War is back on the
table. War is back on the menu.
Pakistan. Pakistan. What kind of people
are
you? Okay. Same. Same at all. says, "I
have had this question since yesterday.
How will the geopolitics between
countries other than other than India
and Pakistan play out simultaneously?
For now, from what I can see right now,
it's a meta war between China and Russia
or the US." Right now, everybody wants
to stay out of this. Xiinping went to
Moscow. He did not stay back in China
when while this thing was going on. And
the Chinese initially once the first
strikes were done of operation by India,
the Chinese kind of condemned it saying
that it is regrettable or something like
that. But they kind of stayed out of it
and the US also said that we want to
stay out of this thing and so on. So
right now everybody is staying out of
this and we'll have to see how it goes.
So the deal is India needs to ensure
that this remains regional. It should
not go beyond the Indian subcontinent.
As long as it doesn't go beyond the
Indian subcontinent, people will stay
out of it mostly. Okay. They have broken
the ceasefire. Now it's it's very much
very much confirmed. very much confirmed
it's broken. The ceasefire is gone.
Pakistan has a huge amount of debt from
China. If India disintegrates Pakistan,
what happens to the debt? It's gone.
It's over. It's finished. Pakist China
can say goodbye to that
debt. All right. I am getting a
tremendous number of comments right now.
Um they have targeted the great temple
of Matavishna Devi Dvi in Lal Chalk. AB
absolutely barbaric behavior.
Unacceptable. They're targeting
religious places, shameless people. They
need to be punished for this in a way
that liberates their people from this
nonsense. Okay. Sudita says there are
UAVs, unmanned aerial vehicles over
Matavishna Devi
temple. Oh man, these people. Okay.
Rashmi says is China behind this to
break the ceasefire by Pakistan because
China doesn't want us to win and they
are the daddy of Pakistan where they are
the daddy of
Pakistan. I think this is not about
China. I think the Pakistanis have no
self-control. I don't think the Pakist
even the Chinese can control the
Pakistanis. I don't think the Chinese
see the Americans try to control the
situation.
H okay. Um what is
this? Okay. Vibore says in the distant
future let's say India takes over
Pakistan. How will the people of
Pakistan emerge with our people? Is it
something even we want to do? Not not
right now. It should you know right now
you cannot integrate the people of
Pakistan with our country with our
people because they are tremendously
radicalized. Okay. And they and they
hate us. I would say about 90% of
Pakistanis want us dead. If they can
kill us they'll kill us.
So you cannot integrate Pakistan with
India right now. If Pakistan breaks up
then we can't integrate the broken up
nations with with in India right now. So
we have to first have a process of der
radicalization several
decades and so on. So there we have it
that that's what needs to happen. My god
the the comments are just flying flying
at the speed of light. Trump must be
livid by this mockery. Well if he has
any sense he should punish Pakistan for
what they've done now. They should he
should punish Pakistan because this is
unacceptable. Uh they are targeting siks
and the religious places to enrage sick
community against the government on
purpose. You see our sick people. They
are not stupid. They are not
stupid. Most sick people in India are
deeply patriotic. They are our people of
course. So the Pakistanis have always
tried to to play this divide and rule
game that they've learned from the
British and so on. So yeah, Amisha says
Pishaw is under attack now. Well, it's
high
time. Okay, this unraveled this
unraveled in less than an hour. Trump
must be livid like like the is saying he
should be he should be. We Gen X says
what do you think will happen in the
next 72 hours? Will Trump again try to
announce his fire? Will India listen to
him once more? I think it's it's a
distinct possibility my friends that by
the time the sun is out tomorrow morning
India could be in possession of some
parts of
Puk. Okay. I think it's a distinct
possibility. This night is going to be a
long
night. Forget about 72 hours. What's the
time right now in India? It's
10:12. So about 8 hours to go for
sunrise. Maybe 7 hours. in 7 hours. My
goodness, who knows what will
happen. It's it's potent. It's possible
that the border will change by tomorrow
morning and and I think Trump should let
it let this happen. Uh Vidi says, "Will
Mr. Modi undo the mistake of British
agent Neu and declare Balojasthan Indian
territory? If no and why we are the same
civilization when Balo gets independent
soon." See, we are the same people. We
are the same blood. The Balo people are
very similar to to the to all the other
people of western
India. Same blood. No question about it.
But please understand this my dear
Indian friends and and everybody
else. Blood doesn't matter. If blood
mattered my friends then Greece and
Turkey would never be at war. Do you
have any idea how much they fought in
the
past? Greece and Turkey are the same
blood. The Turkish
people, 99% of Turkish people are
converted
Greeks. If blood mattered, then the
Turks would not want death to the Greeks
to the Greek people today. But they want
Greece to cease existing. They want
Greece to Greece to stop
existing. Similarly, today the people of
Pakistan, they may they may be my blood,
my relatives, far away, distant
relatives, but they want us dead.
Most of them, I'm not saying all of them
want us dead. Some of them are nice
people. I even have some Pakistani
viewers sometimes and I I wish them
well. I have nothing against them. But
the truth is most of them wish us dead.
Maybe 90% of Pakistan's population wants
us dead. So then what do I do with the
fact that they are my relatives, distant
relatives in same blood. What's the
point? They are not our civilization. We
are not the same civilization.
Civilization is based on culture. They
have chosen a different culture for
themselves.
We don't wish anybody dead but they wish
us dead. So I don't care if they are the
same blood as me. I will defend myself
and my people, my country. And that's
what Mr. Modi is doing. So Baljasthan
probably will not be declared an Indian
territory once it becomes independent
and once Pakistan is is broken up. It
should be declared independent. It
should be declared an Indian
protectorate and so on. There we have
it. Sorab says infiltration of
terrorists in
Jammu.
Really? Really? Is that what what these
guys
want? My
god. My god. It's over. It's over for
Pakistan. Dharma says, "Why did the
Chindu aircraft corporation stock price
shoot up and the salt stock price fall
in the last two days? Does it mean that
we have lost a few Rafal to Chinese
fighters? Is Karan Tapar right? Karan
Tapar is a
disgrace. Let me say that openly. Karan
disgrace. I have no respect for that
individual. Now about the Changdu I've
seen I've not actually gone and seen the
stock prices myself. The media is
reporting this that whatever. Listen,
have we do we have a single piece of
evidence of a Rafal jet which was shot
down or an India Indian fighter plane
which was shot down? Do you think that
in today's day and age where everybody
has one of these things in their in
their pocket? Do you think you can hide
it? If an Indian fighter plane would
have gone down in in in Pakistani
territory, it would have been all over
social media, all over the Pakistani
media, all over CNN, all over everywhere
else. If an Indian fighter plane went
down in Indian
territory, India has millions of people.
They would have taken pictures. They
would have come out. You can't stop
that. You cannot stop
that. Nothing has
happened. We have lost no
Rafals. Okay. So, I don't know these
stock prices, they are affected by
rumors. Do you understand that they are
affected by rumors? Right now, I would
like to see the stock prices of of the
Chinese weapons manufacturers.
H that the who which is the company that
manufactures those Chinese radars and
those Chinese air defense systems and
those Chinese
missiles that don't
explode the
Chinese they have been humiliated along
with the
Pakistanis right so please don't give so
much credence to
rumors okay it's not a it's not a good
practice now okay let's see Tushar says
by do you I think by providing loans to
PO Pakistan by IMF they may so I've
already taken this question so I'll take
it now but I'm just telling you I've
already answered the question like at
least
twice. Uh Aloo says do we have a
Pakistani pilot or not? Look uh I am not
the right person to answer that
question. Uh we may or may not have a a
Pakistani pilot or multiple Pakistani
pilots. The government has not made any
announcements or statements. Uh I've
heard
credible sources very credible sources
say that multiple fighter planes of
Pakistan came down in Indian territory
um etc. But uh look I'll not speculate
okay now what did I just see a million
comments flying around so I'm not able
to latch on to a
comment. Okay I'll just take the latest
comment whatever it is everyone.
everyone. Okay, what do we
have? Um, are we taking Lahore in the
next 10 days? I would love to. I would
love to, but I think we will focus on P
actually. Uh, of course taking Lahore
would be would be great. I don't have
anything against that. It is one of our
ancient great cities. It is
especially significant when it comes to
the history of the Sikh Kingdom Sik
Empire. It was the capital city of
Maharaja of the great Maharaja Ranjit
Singh and Lahore should never have been
given to Pakistan. So I would love to
have Lahore again but do we want that
population the radicalized population in
India? That's the question my friends.
So maybe it's not the best time to have
Lahore but I would love to have it other
anyway just for purely sentimental
reasons. It's one of our great cities.
Um,
okay. Lalai Chuti Yash says, "Why
doesn't the world end the UN
especially?"
Um, after why doesn't the world end the
UN after the Russia Ukan
war? This is off topic, but let me take
it because I I my I clicked on that.
Uh, okay. So, uh, because there are
certain powers like the US, like China,
etc., which still have some use for the
UN, you know. So that's why they will
not uh let it go. The UN is obsolete.
The UN doesn't do any good to the for
the world. The UN doesn't provide any
value to the world. The UN is not in a
position to stop Pakistan from doing
terrorism. The UN is not in a position
or it is unwilling to stop Pakistan from
indulging in terrorism. The US is
unwilling. The UN is unwilling to stop
Pakistan from violating a ceasefire.
It's absolutely useless. But the US then
China and some other nations have some
use for it. That's why they keep it
going.
Okay. Uh Shashir says the US should
punish Pakistan by canceling their IMF
loan. I think forget about the IMF loan
and forget about the US. What we should
do is we should consider what we can do
to punish Pakistan to we should not
depend on others to to dish out
punishment to
Pakistan. It is now time for us to dish
out the
punishment. You want that IMF loan,
enjoy it. You will enjoy it without PK.
you you will and you can use that that
loan to rebuild to rebuild whatever
we're going to destroy in the next 24
hours or or not whatever. So this is it
now this has to be it. This is is
disrespectful to the United States. It's
disrespectful to India. It's dis
disrespectful to President Trump. It's
disrespectful to the people of India to
Prime Minister Modi. Unacceptable. This
the Pakistanis have proven within 1 hour
of the ceasefire announcement that they
cannot be trusted. Now they have to be
eliminated
eliminated. Uh hermit purple says they
are so cooked. India low estimate 17
billion per day high estimate something
per day. Uh okay some some statistics
I'm not able to figure out what exactly
it is but u okay I I'll I'll think about
it later on but thank you for pointing
out the statistics I really appreciate
that okay Sunita says Nagotaa intense
terror activities happening right
now I think Pakistan has signed its
death sentence let us execute
that let's execute that
What Adita says two
beheadings in
Naga. Okay, this is it. You cannot
forgive these people
anymore. This has to end
now. My god. This has to end now.
It will be a different world tomorrow
morning, I think.
Unacceptable.
Unacceptable. This is
unacceptable. I have I am usually not a
very emotional person. I I know how to
control my emotions, but I'm
Yeah, this is unacceptable.
Uh this is a historical question. We'll
take it some other time. My god. So many
ceasefires. My god. My
god. Okay, that's enough. That's that's
that's enough
now.
Um okay. Goyel says, "Why is the
government not giving any briefings on
the latest
updates?" I would say that there's a
good reason for that. When the situation
is so fluid, when it's changing every
five minutes, then the government
should the government is is a
responsible government. It should wait
and watch and once the situation
stabilizes or once we stabilize the
situation, then we should have some kind
of briefing to the world and to our
people. So, I think u it's the right
thing not to just do knee-jerk
reactions, not to not to do knee-jerk
reactions. Hersha says, "Please tell us
what you're feeling right
now. I am feeling multiple emotions. I'm
first of all extremely angry. If that
beheading news is true, that that that
is unacceptable and there is no
forgiving that. And the fact that they
are launching drones again at
us and siren sounding in Gujarat in Bhuj
and blasts over
shinagar you you can't forgive these
people
anymore says Jan from Nepal J Nepal also
my dear friends my dear
friends we are the same people and we we
really appreciate Nepal also for
everything and and we are very sorry
about what happened in in Balgam one
Nepalese citizen died. I'm very sorry
about that. Terrible. And we will avenge
the Nepalese citizen. We
will. All right. Um Kapalin says a blast
was heard in
Peshawar.
Okay. All right. It's it's it's it's
back on. It's on. All right. Arnav says,
"Uh, what's your broad vision for the
future about the future of the temporary
nation? Will it cease to exist by
2031? I think it's there. I think
there's a 50% probability that the map
will be different tomorrow
morning. I think there's a 80%
probability that if it is not different
by tomorrow morning, it will be
different by by the time 72 hours are
out from today from right
now. So that's it. I I don't have any
broad vision for the future of the
temporary nation. Done. Done. This is
it. This is the end of Pakistan. This
has to be the end of Pakistan. We will
never get another opportunity like this.
You know, you cannot just do a war when
you feel like
it. There have to be just causes for
war. And we have been given the just
cause for
war. If we don't take it now, when will
we take it? That's it. It's
done. Uh Russia takes over Ukraine,
China takes over Taiwan, India takes
over PK. Is there a deal as such? Would
be nice if it was so simple. It sounds
very very you know like a very nice
pattern very symmetrical but I don't
think it's like that. I don't think it's
like
that. Namaste Marasha says can you
please say what's the Nagot be
beheading? It seems to have happened
after I started the live stream and I'm
not I'm not I don't know what it is. So
I won't be able to tell you what's
happening in real time. I'm I'm getting
the news on from the live chat over here
right now from what you from what you
all are putting on the live chat. I'm
I'm getting news from
that.
So, so I I don't know but let's see now.
Let's see.
Um Arshia Agarwal says did Pakistan
break the ceasefire to provoke or
because it feels backed into a corner. I
think the Pakistani military is is
feeling absolutely utterly humiliated by
India and they feel like the people of
Pakistan will think that these people
are no longer legitimate rulers of
Pakistan and that's why they're doing
this. Uh KD says third course Bal
Bhalpur being attacked by
drones. Well, make them the zerooth
course core. Wipe them out. Enough
enough of this.
Um Rahul says ceasefire has already been
violated by Pakistan. They have struck
multiple missiles into India. Why would
they do this? What do they have to gain?
I think they they have to show their
people that we are capable of of hurting
India otherwise we are no longer
legitimate. So that's what um okay where
was this uh unacceptable absolutely
unacceptable I completely agree with
you. Uh Abdullah says Pakistan P to take
it back at the cost of any amount of
pain. I would agree with my friend
Abdullah over here. We have to take it
back. Enough is enough. I completely
agree with
you.
Um Chiag says, "What should the local
Indian public do to actually win the
narrative war internationally? Can we
play a role without being at the
border?" Absolutely. Look, you all have
a cell phone or whatever. You all are on
social media. every day spend just five
minutes a day reminding the world that
Pakistan is the nation that hired that
that harbored Usama bin Laden. They are
the nation that created the Taliban.
They are the nation whose citizens flew
aircraft, hijacked aircraft into World
Trade Center towers. They are the nation
that has bled Pak that has bled
Afghanistan, that has bled India, that
that has bled Iran, that bleeds
everybody. They are a terrorist nation.
Remind them every single day. Take five
minutes a day. We have 1.4 billion
people. If even if even onetenth of us,
170 million of us spend 5 minutes a day
doing this every day on social media,
the world won't be able to ignore it.
The Pakistanis won't be able to counter
us. So that's what we need to do. So be
internet warriors for India. Everybody
can pull their weight in this
manner. All right.
Um, okay. Two edited NRS says, "You
answered us the other day about
Pakistan's 10 days or minus 2 days of
remaining munitions. Does the ceasefire
advantage them and let them reload? Yes,
it does. If they had taken, let's say, 5
days off before starting this nonsense
again, then maybe the Turks could have
supplied them with with more drones or
maybe the Chinese would have supplied
them with more whatever." Yeah. But it
looks like no madness. Madness.
Absolutely madness. Okay. Aryan Singh
says, "Pakistan PM latest tweet is
confusing. Please look into it." Let me
see. What's his name? Shabba Sharif.
Shah
Baz Sharif. Let me see what this
individual has
tweeted.
Uh, okay. Let's see. Let's put this on
the tree on the
screen. Let's put this on the screen. Is
it confusing? Shabbaz Sharif, Prime
Minister of the Islamic Republic of
Pakistan says, "We thank President Trump
for his leadership in his proactive role
in for peace in the region. Pakistan's
Pakistan appreciates the United States
for facilitating this outcome which we
have accepted in the interest of
regional peace and stability. We also
thank Vice President JD Vance and
Secretary of State Marco Rubio for their
valuable contributions for peace in
South Asia.
Pakistan believes that this marks a new
beginning in the resolution of issues
that have plagued the region and
prevented its journey towards peace,
prosperity and stability. That's what he
has said. Now let's see what's trending
here. Let's see what's trending if it
loads. Breaking shooting this live drone
engagement over Shiningar with my phone
right now. Big Pakistan drone attack
over Shinagar. It's broken. The
ceasefire has been broken. Pakistan has
immediately broken the ceasefire. So
Vizad is saying Pakistan has launched
suicide drones against targets in Jammu
breaking the fresh ceasefire. So Mr.
Shabbaz Sharif they have betrayed
you. So the Pakistani military has
betrayed their own prime minister. They
have they have slapped President Donald
Trump in his face. They have proven to
the people of India that they cannot be
trusted. Now what do you expect us to
do? What do you expect our prime
minister do? Do does the world expect
our prime minister to just accept this?
H I just don't get it. It's not going to
work
now. This is
it. Rhythm Takur says, "How hard?" Oh,
vampire. How hard would our retaliation
be now? I think it will be all the way
like like like Damon Salvatore or Stefan
Salvatore the
Ripper. It'll be all the way. It's It's
over. It's
over. This This can only end one way
now. My god. What have the Pakistanis
done? What have they
done? Okay. Ata says, "What's the single
most critical event post which the
conflict might might go
nuclear? What would induce the
Pakistanis to to to breach the nuclear
option?"
um what would induce them to do that? I
think they would be very very very very
wary of breaching the nuclear option. I
don't know. I don't know what goes on in
their minds. Okay. I don't know. Our our
army or military or government has a
pretty good idea of how their mind
works. I'm not quite sure what it is. uh
when you do something as irrational as
as
as spurning this great gift that you got
then I I don't know how your mind works.
You can't predict you know what could
they could do
logically but uh we have to punish
them. So if there is a
situation in which our armed forces feel
that you know there could be a
potential possibility of Pakistan trying
something like this then we have to take
appropriate steps to prevent that from
happening and I'm
sure trust me I'm sure we have
contingency measures planned which is
called preemptive
measures okay to take out uh a nuclear
threat before it becomes
active. All right, let's see. The mighty
warrior says, "Could this all be a trap?
Can can this be a trap? Pakistan,
Bangladesh, China and their eyes on our,
as they call it, landlocked states, a
multiffront war. Can could the US be
involved? Could Russia come against
China?" Okay.
Um, a multiffront war. My question is
this. Let's say it's a trap. Let's say
it's a trap and India gets involved in a
multiffront war. What sort of
multiffront war will it be? Let's say
East Pakistan, West Pakistan are both
involved. Is that a big threat for us?
We can deal with both of them at the
same time on two sides of our border.
They are not threats. The only threat is
if China gets involved, but it's not
that easy for China to get involved
because we have the Himalayas up there.
It's not easy for them to make an
incursion into India. And this time we
are very well prepared.
uh and by the time China actually tries
something properly, we could have dealt
with Pakistan east and west Pakistan
both at the same time. And then the
question arises, what does Russia do?
Russia will want to stay neutral and
they would want India to win for their
own selfish reasons and other reasons.
And the US would not want India to be
weakened because they need India against
China. So I don't think it's going to
work that way. I don't think it's going
to work that way.
Chitra says, "Do do the Pakistanis have
the words the the term self-control in
their dictionary?" Looks like they have
absolutely no self-control whatsoever
and they seem to have decided that we
want to dig our own grave. So, well, let
them have
it. Anudipa says, "Does why does Israel
support India so openly and in an
outright way? Do they have some interest
like others or is it legit?" Look,
everybody, every nation acts in its own
self-interest. Whatever action a nation
takes, it's going to be in the service
and in the pursuit of its own national
interest. And that's the way it should
be. There is nothing wrong with that.
And if two nations are in such a
position that their national interests
converge, then there is a great amount
of synergy between the two nations and
the nations then are essentially
considered to be friends. So that's how
it works in geopolitics. There is no
free lunch. There is no nothing like
that. Nothing like that. It's all about
national self-interest and that's the
way it should be. That way you can
reliably predict what a nation will do
and you can reliably tell whether a
nation can be trusted as your friend or
not. So it's fine and Israel and India
have a lot of convergence of interests
which is great and I really like that.
Uh says, "Is all of this done to release
Imran Khan
early by certain people who support
Imran Khan in the army?" I don't think
it's that. I don't think it's that. Uh
Amisha says, "Two civilians and one
soldier are
dead." Well, then let let the Pakistanis
be punished for that. Unacceptable. Uh
Vidi says, "What will happen after
Pakistan loses? We will not have a
threat from their elements external and
internal." Once Pakistan is dealt with
my friends and this is a great question
Vidy Vidi has asked an important
question once this military action is
done and once Pakistan the threat is is
is defanged neutralized then we have
other problems to deal with within India
within Bhat we have a 100 million
illegal infiltrators inside
India from various
nationalities when we revoke the visas
of all Pakistanis tens of thousands of
Pakistan is staying illegally in India
that came to light. Women from Pakistan
who had married Indians and who are
staying since 1960s and 1970s and have
have children in India. How is this
acceptable? What kind of a joke is this
country? So that will have to be dealt
with. Then I think 100 million possibly
illegal Bangladeshes all across India in
your face blatantly openly in your in
your face that will have to be dealt
with and then the far east of India the
cookies the is this country a joke that
we have so many illegal infiltrators
here once we dealt once we once we deal
with Pakistan we're going to have to
deal with these things and it will be
the right time possibly to do that after
this great victory So let us have the
victory first. The Pakistanis have given
us Kasus
bellai you
know the the
uh the cause the right a just cause for
war. Anie Ed says now India needs to do
tand and end it. What do you think? I I
think you're
right. India will never get another
opportunity like this. This is the time.
This is the time to finish
Pakistan once and for all. We will never
have another
opportunity.
Um, Sauturu Goojo, what is the most
powerful missile in the world? It
depends, right? U do you mean how
longest range, greatest
payload output and so on?
The most powerful, the most dangerous
missiles in the world will be missiles
that have nuclear warheads and then
there are multiple variations of that
including missiles that have MIV
capability in which case you have one
missile with like 10 warheads. So those
are even more dangerous and so on. So
you know one of the most powerful
missiles is considered to be the Russian
Sarmat missile. It's called Satan or
something by the west or something. So
maybe that's the one.
US advisory has said that we are out of
this India Pakistan case. Then Trump
came to launch ceasefire. Is the US
secret members forces Trump for that? I
look I can't I I can't speculate about
that. Right. I don't know. Uh the US
first said yeah like you said that they
are staying out of it and then Trump
comes in the way to show how great he is
and now the Pakistanis insult Trump.
They make him look like a fool. I didn't
make him look like a fool. Our country
did not do that. We respected Trump. The
Pakistanis have disrespected him. He
needs to take it out on Pakistan. Take
it out on
Pakistan. Anish Misha says Indian drones
have been reportedly spotted in
Pakistan. So what do the Pakistanis
expect?
Huh? They will violate the ceasefire and
then they will not expect Indian drones
in
Pakistan. Are these people absolutely
mad or
what? Abishek says Pakistan has violated
the ceasefire.
Yeah. Now do you think that India will
retaliate? India will be the world's
stupidest country if we don't take
advantage of this and finish Pakistan
off. I would want to see the Indian army
in PK by tomorrow morning if it's
possible. I think it's possible very
much
possible. Shhat says China has invol has
announced full support to Pakistan. What
now? What now? We should say thank you
to China for showing us your true face
and and to help with you.
Uh we should remain polite on a live
stream,
right? To hell with you and we're going
to do what we need to
do. Uh Anime says, "Is Imran Khan dead?"
I don't know. I don't know. Uh there
have been rumors since yesterday or day
before that uh he's dead,
but I don't know. So we will know
eventually once the the once the dust
once the dust falls once once the dust
settles we'll know whether he's dead or
not. I think we can go to Lahour and
find out for ourselves. Right. Uh Syan
say Saha says how much of our air
defense resources have been exhausted
over the past 4 days. I think we would
have sufficient resources to
last I don't know a month or two. So
some of them would obviously uh have
been used up but I am pretty sure we
would have more than sufficient
resources to to last a long war and to
ensure that you know Pak Pakistan runs
out of all resources. So let's not worry
about that. We we are fine. We we are
very much
fine. Um Kashmir CM says attack happened
whereas TV channels quoting army sources
say no ceasefire happened. I can see
ceasefire has been violated. I don't
know which channels are saying what. It
doesn't matter. The Kashmir CM I think
he is a more credible source than some
random TV channel and I can see the live
coverage of the of the of the anti-
aircraft firing happening and drones
flying in the air and anti- all that. So
it's done. It's done. Okay.
Now, okay. Immune boy says, "I've been
surfing through Twitter lately and I see
a very manipulated image of India in the
eyes of the so-called woke western
dummies. Why are we so hated? Even it's
clear and so
on." They hate us for various reasons.
Okay. One reason is that we are a
polytheistic nation. It's a cultural
thing. They don't like it. We have never
converted like everybody else. We still
are proud polytheists. We are the
world's oldest civilization. They have
not been able to break us. That's one
thing. Another thing is that we are very
we we we we were under British
occupation for 250 years and we have
still not died out. We have still not
been destroyed and we are again rising.
How dare we rise again? They hate
that. You know there's this saying that
you should stay don't don't get off the
don't get off the reservation. Stay in
your lane. All that and we are getting
off the reservation. We are not staying
in our lane. We are making our own
lanes. They hate it. That's why. So
that's why there's this this thing this
image. Okay.
Um Amarinda Dh says if India takes some
part of Pakistan will it dilute the
unity and cause chaos in the in India's
terrorists will have access to all
cities. We have to be very judicious
about this. We have to take back only PK
not the whole of Pakistan. And when we
take back P, we have to quarantine the
population for some time and we'll have
to do it very judiciously. I'm sure all
the plans are in place. So we will have
to be very careful because you are right
the people the the citizens of these
places these regions are all radicalized
and they all hate us. The overwhelming
majority of these people Pakistanis hate
us. You know it is it is so
naive to say that we are the same people
and most Pakistanis have no problem with
India. It's so
naive. Dear Pakistani brothers and
sisters, I know most of you want us
dead. 90% of you want us dead. I know
that. If you get a chance, you'll kill
us. So let us not delude ourselves into
believing that the two nations love each
other and it's only politicians who have
come in the way.
No, it is much deeper than that. So, we
will see about that. All right. All
right. All right. So, what else do we
have? Uh, Deutschand Warrior 2.0 says,
"How is India sovereign if India and the
US have billions of illegal immigrants?"
I think only Russia, China, and maybe
Israel are the only three sovereign
countries in the
world. So, so look, India is not
sovereign. I know that we have illegal
immigrants. The US has illegal
immigrants. Does it make the US a non-s
sovereign
nation? The US can deport each and every
illegal immigrant if they want to. It
was the Biden regime's policy to bring
in illegals, to change the demographics
and to have more voters, illegal voters.
So that's not a loss of sovereignty.
That's a state
policy. Understand that? Now we also
have millions of illegal immigrants. We
must have the highest proportion of
illegal immigrants of any nation in the
world. Yes. But we still even today if
tomorrow the government decides we'll
throw them all out. There is nothing
those 100 million can do. They can cross
some low and order problems for some
time but they can be dealt with by the
state which means we are sovereign. It's
only if we are helpless and even if we
want to throw them out we can't throw
them out that then it's a problem. So
that's that's where we have it. Um all
right what next do we have? Let's take
some other questions.
Um okay utkar says what about turkeys
backstabbing even India helped them
during the earthquake. Uh right so uh
the the thing is this one second let me
see something I saw something
interesting.
[Music]
Um all right the questions are coming in
just thick and fast. Anyway the question
is what about Turkey? Turkey. Yeah
Turkey I'm not surprised with what the
Turks have done. Not surprised at all.
So we helped Turkey when they were in
need. They had these the series of
devastating earthquakes. When was it
last year or whenever it was a series of
devastating earthquakes and we sent
teams of Indian doctors and rescue
personnel and we sent supplies to
Turkey, medical supplies, other supplies
and so on to the people of to help the
people of Turkey unconditionally. We
help them from the goodness of our
heart. And what does the government of
Turkey do in return? They help Pakistan.
They stand with the terrorist nation.
Erdogan Erdogan puts out a tweet saying
that we stand with the brotherly people
of
Pakistan. It's because Pakistan and
Turkey are essentially the same kind of
people, the same kind of nation,
criminal nations. Both nations lack a
history. Instead of a history, both
nations have a criminal record.
So there we have it. So Indians, my dear
friends, my dear Indian friends,
brothers and sisters, please remember,
don't forget the role that Turkey has
played in this matter, right? They have
supported our
enemies. Imagine that. H
um Arjun Nay says the fight that we have
been fighting for so long is physical
but the problem is the ideology also,
right? How do we fix that? You fix that
slowly. An ideological thing or a
cultural thing cannot be fixed
overnight. That takes time. Which is why
we cannot reabsorb Balojasthan or Sindra
or or anything else immediately. We're
going to have to have a slow process of
dradicalizing the people which has to be
done by by reform by by by changing the
education system and and removing the
influence of certain ideologies and so
on. That takes time. That takes time.
The Chinese have been trying to do that
to Tibet for decades. They still haven't
succeeded
completely. They have been doing it very
forcibly with full control over Tibet.
They still haven't s succeeded until
now. They took Tibet in the 1950s.
That's more than almost 80 years ago.
They still haven't been able to sinize
the Tibetan people. So, it takes time.
Please understand
that. All right. Let's see some more
questions.
Um Aditi says the terrorists came
disguised as our army soldiers. Well,
that's I think something they did uh
during the the the Pahelgam attack as
well, right? The Pahelgam massacre. They
came dressed as army soldiers. Standard
Pakistani practice. Standard Pakistani
practice. Shameless
people. Okay. Arian says Pakistani
drones in
Sinagar. Okay. So what happens now? Uh
foreign secretary Vikram Mishi is going
to put out a video message shortly.
Okay. We'll see about that. We'll see
about
that. Deutschan Warrior says, "Why did
Indian air defense system fail for not
being able to take Indian territory from
Pakistani attacks through Turkish drones
and training missiles? What on earth are
you talking about? The Indian air
defense system failed?
What are you talking about? I I think
you're living in a in a different
universe. We the air defense system has
performed
spectacularly. Last night they they they
launched a ballistic missile at New
Delhi. We took it out. We took out
hundreds of drones. We took out hundreds
of missiles. They have tried their best
to hit more than 25 Indian cities. How
many cities have been hit? What are you
talking
about? Okay.
Um, Antari says, "If World War II begins
in a few months after India, Pakistan,
which countries do you think will form
the teams? What will the aftermath of
the war?" Complete speculation. I am
sorry I can't answer that
question.
Um, what will the US and Donald Trump do
now? I think they may try to again have
another ceasefire or or or or to have
ceasefire version two
possibly or maybe Donald Trump gets
angry and he will stop. I don't know.
We'll see. We'll see about that. We'll
see about that. All right.
Um Okay. So many questions, man. I'm I'm
not able to pick a question. It's
disappearing. Okay. Look what is this.
Vignesh says a Pakistan geospatial
agency has partnered with a private US
geospatial agency and high resolution
images of Pahelgam were purchased 3
months before April
22. Uncle's handprint all over it. Check
the article. Uncle as in Uncle Sam.
Yeah, it's possible. You see these I I I
am aware of some some such article that
came out. I haven't read yet but it
looks like they were doing proper
background research on pahela and this
was all very well planned and thought
out. So yeah
interesting now okay animeish says
tribute to Manohar Parikar for getting
us S400 in Rafal thoughts. Manohar
Parikar was a great man. He did so much
to bolster our defenses make us more
Atman. make us more even if not at
completely go in the direction and he
ensure that we purchase the right
weapons systems. So yes, absolutely
tribute to him. Even when he was on his
on his on his la in his last days when
he was about I mean you know when he was
terminally ill even then he was working
towards this. So really great man. We
should uh be grateful to
this for for what he
did. Okay. Now what else do we have?
What is going on?
uh US and China start talks on easing
trade. Is there any connection? I don't
know. We'll see. We'll see. It's too
early to to see to think if there's a
connection between the US China thing
and what's happening here. Essentially,
everything is interconnected. But is the
latest
ceasefire violation and the the the end
of the ceasefire something to do with
China? I'm not
sure. Uh all
right. Okay.
Um why is Molana so obsessed with face
saving? Even by defying okay Arshra Ash
Dogra even by defying US's intervention
I don't know it's madness
madness or maybe the Chinese are asking
him to do it. I don't know if if the
Chinese are paying him more money then
maybe he'll do what the Chinese say.
Possible. Bobby Bobby good to see you
again sir. Is this just a distraction
for something else? It's always a
possibility that this is a distraction
for something else. But what it could it
be a distraction for that is the
question. In case this is true what you
are saying. So we'll have to see. We'll
have to wait and watch and as more
information comes out in the public
domain, we'll be able to see see whether
it was a distraction for something else.
All right. We'll see about that. Amisha
says Ajit Dwal and Chinese foreign
minister hold talks. All right. There's
no harm talking to
everybody. We'll see.
Proud Indian says is it a Chinese
strategy to strategy to make India
engage in war so that foreign goods
manufacturers brought back are brought
back to China. It it could be see it
could be that way. See the Chinese will
certainly benefit if this situation
drags on for months. If Pakistan becomes
India's Ukraine, it will be great for
China. But if this situation is over in
the next 10 days and then Pakistan no
longer exists, then the neighborhood
becomes super stable and that's the
worst possible thing for
China. So the the Chinese would love to
have the situation go on forever and it
is in our interest to put an end to this
on our own without depending on the US
or somebody else.
So yeah, if this continues, it's great
for China and it'll be bad for India. So
we have to act decisively now. That's
what we need to do. Uh Hersh Johan says
MEA briefing in a short time. All right,
we'll see about that. We'll see about
that. Then we will have some more
information as to what happens. Now, now
what do we have?
Um okay, Sergeant Skylin says India has
Russian arms. is are these Russian
weapons superior to the Chinese arms
that Pakistan has? I heard that Russia
did not want to sell the S400 to China.
Well, the Chinese also have the S400 and
the Chinese would have really wanted
Russia not to sell the S400 to
India. But and I'm sure that privately
they must have applied pressure on
Russia to not sell the S400 to India.
Clearly the Russians resisted the
Chinese pressure and sold the
S400 to India. All right. So u the S400
I think it's one of the best air defense
systems in the world. And then coming to
the other part of your question, India
has Russian arms and the Chinese the
Pakistanis have Chinese weapons. I think
Russian weapons are superior to Chinese
weapons. They are they're superior. So
whatever weapon systems we have, we have
a milange, a mix of various kinds of
weapon systems. We have the French
fighter plane Raval, we have the French
Mirage, we have the Sukoy 30 MKI which
is the Russian system. Um we have the
MiG 21s which is
Russian. We used to have the Mig
whatever Foxbat which is now retired
which is again Russian. We have the
Tajas which is mostly Indian. Then we
have guns bow force guns which are
Swedish. We have other guns that are
Indian. We have the Akash system that is
Indian with the Barak which is Indo
Israeli I can go on forever. So we have
a milange a mix of things. Um and
overall it's it's superior to what the
Pakistanis have. So that's great. I
think Vikram Misri our foreign secretary
is now uh giving some kind of a
statement. We will see. I'm sure my
viewers will let me know what
[Music]
happened. Okay. What what what else do
we have? Animeish says, "Will we have a
live stream tomorrow?" Yes, we will have
a live stream tomorrow. Same time, 8:00
p.m. tomorrow. I'll do that for sure.
For sure. Uh, so yes, Anime, we will do
a live stream tomorrow. Dave Converse
says, "What are the possible ends end
states of this situation?" Okay, let us
consider the scenarios. What can happen?
We had a ceasefire. We had agreed to the
ceasefire under US pressure. Let's say
now the ceasefire has been violated. The
question is what happens now?
One scenario is that President Trump
again pressurizes us to take the
ceasefire and we give into that. That is
not a good option for
India. Second
option is we continue the war. In case
we continue the war, we have to achieve
our geopolitical
objectives. Which means we have to take
back P and we have to completely we have
to inflict a permanent defeat on
Pakistan. A comprehensive military and
political defeat in Pakistan and that
defeat should be such that it will cause
the
end of the Pakistani military and the
dissolution of Pakistan. That is what
needs to happen.
So I think the best possible scenario
right now in the next 72 hours is that
we take back PK. The worst possible
scenario is that we again agree to
another another
ceasefire which uh would would would be
bad. Uh so we will see we will see I
think Mr. Vikram Misri our our foreign
secretary probably is saying is making a
statement right now. Uh he says that the
Indian forces have been given orders to
respond strongly to Pakistani violations
of the ceasefire. Apparently that's what
he says and we'll see and we'll see what
happens. So ceasefire violations are
happening and the government seems to be
holding Pakistan accountable. It's been
a very brief statement. So we will see
about that and uh I let's see I I'll
keep an eye on this thing. Okay. Uh
Anjali says is it possible that China or
the US was only involved in breaking the
ceasefire? is that so it's so weird that
the US said it's none of their business
and then they are stepping in and then
the ceasefire is broken in a few hours.
It's it's see the US always does this.
When you are a super powerful nation,
you can change your mind at a moment's
notice. Others will call it hypocrisy
and they'll say we we can do it. So we
why do we do it? Because we can.
Chinghan is to say why do I conquer?
Because I can. That sort of thing. So uh
it is the privilege of the powerful to
be able to act in a hypoc hypocritical
manner. Uh so yesterday JD van says it's
none none of our business. Today Trump
says I make it my business and he
imposes a ceasefire on us. Um so it's
not weird it's to be expected. The US
will always behave like this and we are
not that powerful that they can say no
to them at this point in time. Uh now is
the the other question is is it possible
that China or the US was involved in
breaking the ceasefire? Look the US
wants a ceasefire. They want Pakistan to
continue to exist so that they can have
some leverage over India. So it is not
in the US's interest for the ceasefire
to be broken but maybe it's in China's
interest if they they calculate that
this could be become India's uh Ukraine
kind of situation or something. So I
think more than the US it is more likely
that maybe China would have induced
Pakistan to break the ceasefire possibly
but we are only speculating at this
point in time but it's an interesting
question. Interesting question. Okay.
Now,
um, Luffy uh, Luffy say, "Okay, first of
all, welcome to our new member. I really
appreciate that, Parvakumar. I never
ever ask anybody to become a member, but
some people still do that. So, I really,
really appreciate that. Thank you so
much. Thank you so much." Now, there was
this question by LA. What is Pakistani
military smoking? I have no idea what
they're smoking. Maybe it's very strong
Afghan stuff, hashish or something. I
don't know. Crazy. completely irrational
behavior. Okay. Geopolitical dub says
the Chinese missile will be recovered.
We have recovered a Chinese missile.
Yes. So do you think the CCP will be
worried about it? It's obviously bad for
the CCP for the Chinese Communist Party
because their technology is now exposed
and we will be able to study it
thoroughly. Clearly, it's not great
technology, but I'm sure there is
something we can learn from that. Yeah.
What sort of seeker do they does the
missile have and and so on. So yeah,
they they'll be worried and concerned.
And the bigger concern is that we will
now uh share that with the United
States. So Omaker says, "Can Pakistan
get the S400 from Turkey?" I don't think
that's possible.
Um I'm sure the Russians have some
safeguards in the S400. I'm sure they
have some safeguards. And even if the
Turks sell it to Tur to to ch to
Pakistan, they'll have to provide
training and all that. You know the S100
is an extraordinarily complicated
system. You need a certain amount of IQ
to be able to operate that. It's very
complex. I'm sure the Pakistanis are
also as intelligent as us. It's not
we're the same people genetically but um
you know to impart the training and all
it's very difficult. So I think it's
it's unlikely that that Pakistan can get
it from Turk. Now let us see let us see
let us see. Mr. says they can't afford
it to sell it to uh Pakistan. Maybe,
maybe. Okay. I don't know. Sod Kore
says, "Is Imran Khan killed? If he gets
killed, will there be a civil war?" I
think if Iran Khan is eliminated by the
ISI or the military, then there could be
a civil war in Pakistan. But is he I
mean this this rumor is circulating on
social media for the past 2 to three
days. I am not sure if that is true, if
that is the case. So, uh so I can't
answer your question because I don't
have the information. But yeah, it's
important to keep an eye on the the
Immran Khan situation. So all of us we
can do that. Okay. Aditya says our
minister said that that Pakistan has
violated the ceasefire. Yeah, that's it.
That is it. Now we do what what needs to
be done. Yeah. M Mr. Msri has said that
Pakistan has violated the ceasefire
agreement.
Um and we have given free hand to our
forces to retaliate in the appropriate
manner.
to respond strongly. We have ordered our
forces to respond strongly. Um, okay.
This is completely we will not take this
question right now. Uh, wait. What do we
have? What
else? Okay. Uh, what other questions do
we have? I think we have gone way past 3
hours now. So maybe we should Okay.
Samarad says India's safety and security
is paramount. India's safety and
security are an integral component of
India's national interest and India's
national interest always must be
paramount for
India and the only guiding factor in our
actions and the choices we make should
be what is the
right course of action considering our
national
interest. Absolutely right. So there we
have it.
Uh Mayor says is Pakistan capable and
will it try to attack central cities
other than near border uh like various
cities is it a concern we should be
prepared for all scenarios and I promise
you we are prepared for all scenarios so
so don't worry too much don't worry too
much gurov says if India takes back PK
how will Pakistan occupied Kashmir
citizens be reabsorbed are they also not
radical it'll be difficult but we'll
have to find some way of doing it but at
least we We have to take back PK because
otherwise the Pakistanis can keep
claiming that the Kashmir issue exists.
There there's something called the
Kashmir issue. There is no Kashmir
issue. This a Pakistan issue. So we have
to take back P to end this nonsense of
the so-called Kashmir so-called Kashmir
dispute. Uh right. So now some people
are saying what are they saying? One
second. One second. Where is it? Where
is it? Okay. Sum says it we just did an
MEA conference which made us look weak.
Look, look people
look when the government makes
statements h we have to be very careful
to tell the world that you know what we
are doing our best to have peace. We
really really want this ceasefire.
Please Pakistan please please understand
we want this
ceasefire. We have to say this. Please
understand my dear friends that
statements that are made
verbally are not the same as actions on
the
ground and it is very important to make
the right statements so that we can take
certain actions. So if we tell the world
that we have tried over and over and
over again for a
ceasefire h and then eventually we go
and take P then we can tell the world we
tried our best. We tried so many times
but these people didn't give us the
opportunity. But if we make a very
strong aggressive press conference then
the world can paint us as the
aggressors. Please understand this.
Please please have a little maturity my
friends. All
right.
Okay. Um so please take the statements
that are made diplomatically with a few
grains of salt. Please understand there
are multiple considerations and multiple
layers here. Sangeit is very upset.
Historical blunder. Wait, wait, wait.
Have some patience. Let let's wait and
watch.
Um, Pragal says, "Is this not enough to
declare war?" Yeah, we will. We will
declare war when the right time is is
going to come. Maybe at 2:00 a.m. in the
morning or something like that. We'll
see about that. We'll see about that.
Um, we shot down an F-16 aircraft. Can
we examine its engine? of we can examine
whatever is available to at our
disposal. If it's not completely
damaged, we can examine the engine. We
can do something about it, right? But
the government hasn't officially
announced that we have taken down F-16s.
We don't want to um um you know, we we
we want to be considerate about the
feelings of our American friends and we
don't want to embarrass them. So, so
yeah. So, Nihar says India hasn't called
off the ceasefire. You see, we should
not call off the ceasefire. We should
say over and over again, we are still
trying for the ceasefire. We are se
still fire trying for the ceasefire and
so on. Okay, now where was this
question? Uh this is one second. Oh, I
was trying to pick something. Where is
it? Okay,
here. Chundra Chri says, "How can I see
if my question got answered?" I asked on
chat and went offline for a bit. Uh you
can see it when when the when when you
you see the replay of this live stream,
but I'm not sure I've taken your
question. So instead of asking this, you
should ask the actual question. Uh okay.
Anyway, you can try again because there
are so many people who are asking
questions. I'm getting like 100
questions a minute. So it won't be
possible for me to take everyone's
questions
unfortunately. Um
uh Aush where is it gone? Question is
gone very very rapidly. It's going away.
Aritra says now does taking P means
clash with China as CPC and China Afghan
alternate route goes through P. Uh
please take my question also show on the
map. Okay, let's Where's the map?
Where's the map? Here is the map. Okay,
now the question is P and what does
China do about it? So, it will all
depend on the rapidity or lack of it in
which we take back P. P is these places.
See, uh, Scaru, uh, Hunza, Gilgit, all
of this is P. Now, that is our
territory, but it's currently illegally
occupied by Pakistan and it makes sense
for us to take it back. So the question
you're asking is what does China do
about this? It all depends on how
quickly we establish our hold on P.
First of all, you have to enter P,
defeat the the terrorists, Pakistanis
who are holding it and then once they're
defeated, you establish your command and
presence and and hold over it. So that
takes some time. The faster you do it,
the less China has a chance of of
stopping you. So that's how it goes. Now
what else questions do we have? Okay,
Chandra is back asking why all other
countries intelligence agencies do not
stand up to India and own up that yes we
know that India hit terrorist locations
only. It's because every country has its
own selfinterest and they don't care
about the interests of others and most
countries don't want India to rise too
much especially western countries
because they're jealous because of the
history.
So you see the
world we we we think that the world runs
operates on the basis of satya jay it
does not everybody looks out for their
own self-interest nobody gives you a
free lunch nobody helps you out for free
if you want some help from them they
expect something in exchange in return
so all the country all the other
countries intelligence agencies may have
the information that India is the victim
and Pakistan is a terrorist nation but
does any country say that does any
western country acknowledge the fact
that the Pakistanis are terrorists? They
don't because there's no need for them
to do it and they don't want to help
India out. They're jealous that India
after all these centuries of foreign
occupation is still not dying and we are
actually rising now. They don't like it.
The west wants to remain the number one
entity in the world. They don't want any
eastern nation, any polytheistic nation,
a nation like India to rise. So why will
they help us? They won't help us. Please
understand that that's that's how the
world works. The whole world will ask
you for proof. Proof
proof. Okay. I saw a question about Akai
Chin somewhere but it disappeared
because the questions are flying so
fast. Okay. I'm going to take a couple
more questions and then we will be done.
Sedarth is super angry. Don't know what
to do. How to channelize this anger on
Pakistan? What can a normal citizen do?
If you are super angry, you want to take
it out somewhere then go on social media
and put out the fact about Pakistan. do
it every day. Right? Pakistan, what is
its track record like? The nation that
harbored Osama bin Laden. He stayed in
that nation for a decade. Right? Put out
all these facts. They are the nation
that created the Taliban. They are the
nation that sent terrorists into Mumbai
and Kasab was caught alive. That's why
we know it. And so on. So take it out on
Pakistan on social media. There's no
need to be abusive. They can there's a
nice way to do it and so on.
So, so let me take one more question and
then we will end today's live stream
because it's way past 3 hours but we
will continue this tomorrow. So, right.
Okay. Okay. Ah says Abhir says is
Pakistan of significant interest to
USA? Yeah. All that.
Uh so yeah the US still sees some value
in Pakistan as an as some kind of
leverage over India as long as Pakistan
exists and it's it's a nuisance they can
always blackmail India with Pakistan or
they can say say to India that you know
we'll make Pakistan behave when you do
this for us that sort of thing right so
now okay okay okay
okay all right all right what else shall
I take any more questions
Um Jay Dikshit. Okay, this will be the
last question for today. Jikshit says
after taking P back, what about Shak Gum
Valley? How are we going to deal with
China with that? We'll think about it
when we come to that. First take P back
Shakum is in Chinese hands. We'll see
about that. This is not the right time
to take back Shakum or or Axa Chin. Not
now. That we can do in the future. right
now take back PK we have to think of
about this as a long process one step at
a time focus on what you're doing right
now when you're playing cricket you're
playing one ball at a time right you
should not think about next 15 overs
think about the the ball that's coming
to you that's how we do it and that's
what we need to do all right okay
apparently Shabbaz Sharif will address
the nation at 11:35 p.m. SD. We'll see
about that. We'll see about
that. Okay. I think I can do this all
night, but I need to stop at this point
in time. So, I'm going to end this live
stream right now. Tomorrow, 8:00 p.m.
India time, I'll do another live stream.
I'm sure it's going this situation is
going to evolve and who knows what we're
going to see tomorrow morning. So, we'll
see about that. Okay. So, I'm going to
end it over here now. Thank you so much
for all your questions and I will see
you all tomorrow. Thank you so much.
Stay positive and support support your
nation. Thank you so much. I'll see you
tomorrow.